<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weapons of Kalijor on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weapons of Kalijor on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chavan</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/chavan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/chavan/</guid>
      <description>Chavan is the staff given to Katrina Thorindal by Dorin. It is forged of a rare earth metal alloy that makes it lighter than most wooden staves and stronger than most tempered metals. In addition, Dorin imbued the staff with several magical abilities as he forged it. It is a light grey in color and covered from tip to tip in dwarvish runes that make no coherent sense. It’s unique powers include the ability for the staff to create a small pool of cool, pure drinking water by leaving it laying prone on the ground for a moment, the ability to attract small game animals by stabbing the staff into the ground and letting it stand for a few moments, and the ability to cast a steady, white light, of similar intensity to a high quality torch by tapping one of its ends against the ground several times repeatedly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Destra</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/destra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/destra/</guid>
      <description>Destra is the wicked, black sword wielded by Malice. It is a sword of similar dimensions to a bastard sword, although a touch longer. Destra was forged in a magical fire by a dwarven smith and quenched in the blood of innocents killed by ritual sacrifice. The sword is coal black from tip to handle, it&amp;rsquo;s only mark of color being a deep, navy blue sapphire set into the pommel of the weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elkorine</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/elkorine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/elkorine/</guid>
      <description>Elkorine is a short sword that was forged by the elves that would later become known as the enigmatic Obscuri, long before the great wars. The sword has been carried by many individuals throughout its life, almost all of whom have become notable in some regard or other. The weapon has a tendency to turn up in the hands of the less likely people in history and is said to have a mind of its own, although no one can recall or find evidence of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selendria</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/selendria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/selendria/</guid>
      <description>Selendria is the name of Jumah&amp;rsquo;s magical weapon. It was forged by an ancient elven smith and has been passed down through his family for centuries. The weapon is a small shaft of about 4 feet in length that is capped on either end by a straight, narrow blade, each about 2 feet in length. The weapon is a powerful magical item that allows its wielder to parry or block magical bolts and other similar attacks, harmlessly dissipating them into the air around the weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zyrik</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/zyrik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/zyrik/</guid>
      <description>Zyrik the Dragon Slayer was forged by the dwarven masters in the mystical forges of Kalek&amp;rsquo;Tinal untold ages ago. The weapon was created with the singular purpose of laying waste to the scourge of dragons that had befallen Kalijor and crushed the will of its people beneath their scaly might. The weapon is imbued with the power to do incredible amounts of damage to beings with draconic blood coursing through their veins but its most devastating power was not even conceived of by the greatest craftsmen and mages on Kalijor until the day it was invoked by its wielder.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>