<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology of the Future on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology of the Future on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Gravity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/artificial_gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/artificial_gravity/</guid>
      <description>title: Artificial Gravity desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Artificial_Gravity percent: 100 authors:
Artificial gravity is created, in most cases, by placing a disk made of super-conducting material inside a sealed environment. The disk is suspended within a magnetic field so that it can not touch any portion of its casing, and then spun at extreme velocities (Approximately 130,000 RPM). This creates a gravito-magnetic field that extends outward from the device in a 100 ft radius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body Armor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/body_armor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/body_armor/</guid>
      <description>title: Body Armor desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Body_Armor percent: 100 authors:
Personal protective body armor comes in a variety of shapes, styles and materials, most of which are designed for specific conditions, or to protect against specific forms of damage. For the purposes of simplicity, the records here are broken down into categories describing the physical composition or properties of the armor type in question, such as soft, or hard, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/communications/</guid>
      <description>title: Communications desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Communications percent: 100 authors:
The standard communication medium of the day has become sub-space. Sub-space is mathematically defined as an infinite space that exists within our realm inside a finite boundary. It was discovered in the past 300 years that in any given sub-space realm there is a direct correlation between each point in that realm and each point within our own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computers</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/computers/</guid>
      <description>title: Computers desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Computers percent: 100 authors:
Over centuries of development, computer technology has continued to grow and evolve. After the industry maxed out the capabilities of standard semi-conductor chips they moved on to super-conducting materials and then to the inevitable optical systems, allowing computers to operate at relativistic speeds. Today&amp;rsquo;s computers are all optical processing units that operate on a hexadecimal base programming system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybernetics</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/cybernetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/cybernetics/</guid>
      <description>title: Cybernetics desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Cybernetics percent: 100 authors:
Cybernetics is the science of replacing normal biological parts with artificial ones that fill the same roll. In the beginning of the 20th century it began with pace-makers and artificial hearts and from there developed at a break-neck pace until before long any organ in the human body, with the exception of the spine and brain, could be easily replaced with an artificial equivalent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Shields</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/energy_shields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/energy_shields/</guid>
      <description>title: Energy Shields desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Energy_Shields percent: 100 authors:
Energy shields come in a couple of different forms. The earliest forms of energy shielding for space craft were nothing more than sophisticated tracking algorithms designed to track incoming debris and then vaporize it with a ship&amp;rsquo;s weapon systems. This system proved to be effective, however costly in terms of computer power, sensor usage, and energy consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/interstellar_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/interstellar_travel/</guid>
      <description>title: Interstellar Travel desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Interstellar_Travel percent: 100 authors:
Super-Luminal propulsion is a relatively new science as far as practical application is concerned. There are currently two very different technologies in use by space craft. Gravitic drives, and Traction drives.
Gravitic drives harness the power of gravity to propel a space craft faster than the speed of light. By focusing a beam of focused gravitons, the craft is able to push itself away from solid matter with great force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riana&#39;S Body</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/rianas_body/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/rianas_body/</guid>
      <description>title: Riana&amp;rsquo;S Body desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Riana&amp;rsquo;S_Body percent: 100 authors:
Riana’s cybernetic body is arguably a product of the most advanced and forward thinking technology known to mankind. It is designed to almost perfectly mimic a normal human body in nearly every way as far as construction and structure are concerned, but enhances, strengthens, and builds upon that construction and form immeasurably. Her skeleton is composed of a carbon-carbon honeycomb that is laced/reinforced and sheathed in 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft Technology</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/spacecraft_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/spacecraft_technology/</guid>
      <description>title: Spacecraft Technology desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Spacecraft_Technology percent: 100 authors:
Space craft are now fairly commonplace with models available for prices that the upper middle class can begin to afford. Space travel is still not tightly regulated in open space, although flying in or near an inhabited body (Meaning planet, moon, asteroid, space station, etc) requires a pilot’s license and all of the appropriate clearances from ground control for the air-space in question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weapon Technology</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/weapon_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/weapon_technology/</guid>
      <description>title: Weapon Technology desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Weapon_Technology percent: 100 authors:
With all of the advances in technology that seem to permeate the everyday lives of the citizens of the Sol System it is often asked, why are there not more advanced weapons in use? The answers are myriad and varied depending upon whom you are speaking to, however there are a few that are commonly cited, and ring true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ntrastellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/intrastellar_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/intrastellar_travel/</guid>
      <description> title: Intrastellar Travel desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Intrastellar_Travel percent: 100 authors:
Chemical
Nuclear/Anti-Matter
Solar
Ion/Plasma
Category:Technology&amp;mdash; title: Intrastellar Travel
permalink: /Intrastellar_Travel/ </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>