<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People of the Future on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People of the Future on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alina Martin</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/alina_martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/alina_martin/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Alina Martin Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Independant Operator Date of Birth: February 23, 3015 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;10&amp;rdquo; Weight: 140 lbs Hair Color: Green Eye Color: Bright Green Physical Description: Alina Martin has a runner&amp;rsquo;s body, which she works regularly to maintain. Her naturally bright green eyes come from her father&amp;rsquo;s side of the family, and when she graduated high school, she purchased gene-therapy to change her hair color to match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almon Genloe</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/almon_genloe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/almon_genloe/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Almon Genloe Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Crime Lord Date of Birth: October 18, 2990 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo; Weight: 200 lbs Hair Color: Dark Brown Eye Color: Grey Physical Description:
General Description Almon is a discerning businessman, with a pronounced ability to keep business, pleasure, and personal life, all in their own separate compartments. He dresses like a millionaire (which he is, several times over), treates his employees with respect, and his enemies, even more so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anja Reyals</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/anja_reyals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/anja_reyals/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Anja Reyals Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Unknown Date of Birth: Unknown Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo; Weight: 350lbs (looks around 125lbs) Hair Color: Icy Blue Eye Color: Cobalt Blue Physical Description: Anja looks to have an athletic build, despite her weight which is caused by her unique body. She has long, tapered ears, light blue eyes and dark blue hair that, when unrestrained, reaches the small of her back. With the exception of her eye and hair color, and the absence of any tattoos she is an exact physical copy of Riana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/april/</guid>
      <description>title: April desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: April percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: APRIL (Actualized Personal Relativistic Intelligence Link) Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Pincher, personal support for Daray Bowen Date of Birth: January 1, 3047 Height: NA (About 6 feet in cyberspace) Weight: NA (Looks to weigh about 120 pounds in cyberspace) Hair Color: NA (Glowing yellow in cyberspace) Eye Color: NA (Glowing green in cyberspace) Physical Description: While cyberjacking APRIL appears as a six foot tall, athleticly built, glowing female with flowing, gravity-defying hair down to her waist and glowing green eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bartholomew (Bart) Jankoweitz</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/bartholomew_bart_jankoweitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/bartholomew_bart_jankoweitz/</guid>
      <description>title: Bartholomew (Bart) Jankoweitz desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Bartholomew_(Bart)_Jankoweitz percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Bartholomew (Bart) Jankoweitz Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Neuro-Psychologist Date of Birth: April 7, 3012 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo; Weight: 185lbs Hair Color: Sandy Blond Eye Color: Icy Blue Physical Description: He is a tall man with sandy blond hair, fair skin and icy blue eyes. He is outgoing, very personable and gets very excited about new and interesting things concerning people’s brains and how they react to stimuli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Base Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/base-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/base-line/</guid>
      <description>title: Base Line desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Base-Line percent: 100 authors:
Base-line Humans are people that have less than 10% cybernetic parts (not counting cosmetic alterations that are easily removed) or less than 1% genetic alterations. These people are about as regular as is possible with no real special abilities or powers to speak of. Base-line humans make up the majority by far, more than 90% of the known population of the Sol system).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daray (Dare) Bowen</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/daray_dare_bowen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/daray_dare_bowen/</guid>
      <description>title: Daray (Dare) Bowen desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Daray_(Dare)_Bowen percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Daray (Dare) Bowen Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Pincher (corporate espionage expert) Date of Birth: July 18, 3047 Height: 4’9” Weight: 118 lbs (looks like she couldn’t weigh more than 90 lbs) Hair Color: Strawberry Blonde Eye Color: Dark Cobalt Blue Physical Description: Short and almost scary thin, Daray is actually a lot tougher than she seems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darren Owen Erricson</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/darren_owen_erricson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/darren_owen_erricson/</guid>
      <description>title: Darren Owen Erricson desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Darren_Owen_Erricson percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Darren Owen Erricson Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Private Courier Date of Birth: December 25, 3027 Height: 6’4” Weight: 180 lbs Hair Color: Dark Brown Eye Color: Hazel-green Physical Description: Physically Darren is in amazing shape. He has the toned body of a tri-athlete due to his regularly Parkouring around the Venus Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissidents</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/dissidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/dissidents/</guid>
      <description>title: Dissidents desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Dissidents percent: 100 authors:
Any person or persons who have either chosen, or have been forced to live &amp;lsquo;off the grid&amp;rsquo;. These people are not citizens of The Conglomerate and are treated as lower than second-class people by any Conglomerate personnel who may encounter them. It is technically illegal for Dissidents to enter, leave, or simpley be, inside any Conglomerate facility or vessel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emil Frederick, Phd</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/emil_frederick_phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/emil_frederick_phd/</guid>
      <description>title: Emil Frederick, Phd desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Emil_Frederick,_Phd percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Emil Frederick, PHD Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Bio-Engineer/Doctor of Genetic Sciences Date of Birth: November 3, 2993 Height: 6 feet, 1 inch Weight: 190 pounds Hair Color: Dark brown, peppered with grey Eye Color: Bright hazel-green Physical Description: Doctor Emil Frederick is medium height and slightly overweight build, but not unhealthily so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayle Dyson</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gayle_dyson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gayle_dyson/</guid>
      <description>title: Gayle Dyson desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Gayle_Dyson percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Gayle Dyson Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Doctor of Genetic Sciences Date of Birth: October 11, 3005 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;10&amp;rdquo; Weight: 130lbs Hair Color: Blond Eye Color: Steel Grey Physical Description: Gayle is nearly six feet tall with long blond hair that is nearly always tied back in a tight bun and steely grey eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gene-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gene-line/</guid>
      <description>title: Gene Line desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Gene-Line percent: 100 authors:
Gene-line Humans are individuals who have either undergone extensive genetic alteration, or are the offspring of extensively altered individuals. The extent of genetic engineering is almost unlimited and nearly anything is possible, from simply altering the color of a person’s eyes or hair, all the way to rebuilding their body from the ground up to be anything that is desired, from an elf to a minotaur, ‘aliens’ and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Shantal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gregory_shantal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gregory_shantal/</guid>
      <description>title: Gregory Shantal desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Gregory_Shantal percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Gregory Shantal Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Date of Birth: Unknown (Assumed to be in his 70&amp;rsquo;s) Height: 6&amp;rsquo;3&amp;rdquo; Weight: 515lbs (looks around 160lbs) Hair Color: Grey/Silver Eye Color: Blue Physical Description:
General Description Gregory Shantal is a mercenary that has earned himself a well deserved reputation as a brutal and efficient soldier. He hires himself out to the highest bidder and does not care what kind of work they ask him to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jax Arianas</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jax_arianas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jax_arianas/</guid>
      <description>title: Jax Arianas desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Jax_Arianas percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Jax Arianas Aliases: Avatar/Player: Exodus Occupation: Senior Network Security Administrator, Solidarity Online Date of Birth: August 3, 3009 Height: 6&amp;rsquo; Weight: 200lbs Hair Color: Brown Eye Color: Grey Physical Description: Jax is about six feet tall with dark hair that he keeps short so as to create a minimum of personal grooming time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonin Himabari</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jonin_himabari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jonin_himabari/</guid>
      <description>title: Jonin Himabari desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Jonin_Himabari percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Jonin Himabari Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Martial Arts Instructor for Solidarity Online Date of Birth: 2985 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;8&amp;rdquo; Weight: 110lbs Hair Color: Dark Brown Eye Color: Brown Physical Description: He is a smaller man of Asian descent, although he has never discussed his lineage with anyone so his exact parentage is unknown. He is fairly short, light and trim, fit and strong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaden Mcginley</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/kaden_mcginley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/kaden_mcginley/</guid>
      <description> title: Kaden Mcginley desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Kaden_Mcginley percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Kaden McGinley Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Runner Date of Birth: Height: Weight: Hair Color: Eye Color: Physical Description:
General Description Friend of Alina Martin and Niko Nori
Skills of Note Equipment of Note History Spoilers Status: Living
category:People_Future&amp;mdash; title: Kaden McGinley
permalink: /Kaden_McGinley/ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lana Frederick</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/lana_frederick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/lana_frederick/</guid>
      <description>title: Lana Frederick desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Lana_Frederick percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Lana Frederick (Maxalis) Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Former Prostitute, turned freelance adventurer Date of Birth: May 12, 3023 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;7&amp;rdquo; Weight: 115lbs Hair Color: Royal Blue with white streak Eye Color: Golden Yellow Physical Description: Lana has a toned body of medium height with stark, nearly alabaster skin, golden yellow eyes, and dark, royal blue hair with a white streak running fertically through it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niko Nori</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/niko_nori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/niko_nori/</guid>
      <description> title: Niko Nori desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Niko_Nori percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Niko Nori Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Retired Runner Date of Birth: Height: 5&amp;rsquo;7&amp;rdquo; Weight: 185lbs Hair Color: Black Eye Color: Brown Physical Description:
General Description Alina Martin&amp;rsquo;s frined, partner, and lover.
Skills of Note Equipment of Note History Spoilers Status: Living
category:People_Future&amp;mdash; title: Niko Nori
permalink: /Niko_Nori/ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuiri Qatnio</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/nuiri-qatnio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/nuiri-qatnio/</guid>
      <description>title: Nuiri Qatnio desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Nuiri-Qatnio percent: 100 authors:
(Noo-e-ree Kat-nee-oh) A Nuiri-Qatnio is the extremely rare occurrence of a child of a Psi-line and a Gene-line character, that inherits the majority of the genetic traits/abilities/features from BOTH of their parents. Most Nuiri-Qatnios die within 1D4 years of being born due to the extreme nature of the forces at work within their bodies. Those that do survive, usually have a difficult life ahead of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psi Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/psi-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/psi-line/</guid>
      <description>title: Psi Line desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Psi-Line percent: 100 authors:
Psi-Line Humans are those that have undergone extensive modification through genetic engineering or are the children of thusly-engineered individuals. The end result of the genetic engineering is that the Psi-line humans have developed psionic powers to some extent. The range of their powers varies greatly from one individual to the next, but none of them has anything less than minor psionic aptitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resonance</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/resonance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/resonance/</guid>
      <description>title: Resonance desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Resonance percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Resonance (Real name unknown) Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Singer/Entertainer Date of Birth: Unknown Height: Exact Height Unknown, looks to be just under six feet. Weight: Unknown, looks to weigh around 130lbs Hair Color: Metallic Platinum Eye Color: Golden yellow Physical Description: Resonance looks elvish, with a slight build and elegant features. She has long, tapered ears that end in delicate points and she appears to use them to express emotions much like the elves in Kalijor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samantha Cobb</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/samantha_cobb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/samantha_cobb/</guid>
      <description>title: Samantha Cobb desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Samantha_Cobb percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Samantha Georgia Cobb Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Medical Doctor and Doctor of Cybernetics Date of Birth: February 18, 3008 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;8&amp;rdquo; Weight: 135lbs Hair Color: Dark Aubern Eye Color: Hazel Green Physical Description: Sam is a woman of medium height and build with dark hair and hazel eyes. She tends to dress simply but smartly and does her best not to draw attention to the fact that she is considerably wealthy, both by inheritance and from her practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/sean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/sean/</guid>
      <description>title: Sean desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Sean percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: SEAN Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Date of Birth: Height: N/A Weight: N/A Hair Color: N/A Eye Color: N/A Physical Description:
General Description An Artificial Intelligence designed specifically for use by Emil Frederick in his personal shuttle, The Kitsune. SEAN is responsible for the operation of the ship as well as being Doctor Frederick&amp;rsquo;s personal companion during his self-imposed exile from all things corporate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tech-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tech-line/</guid>
      <description>title: Tech Line desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Tech-Line percent: 100 authors:
Tech-Line Humans are those who have undergone extensive bionic or cybernetic augmentation, to the extent that some have less than 5% of their original body mass still intact. Not all Tech-lines are completely mechanical however, although the majority are over 50% artificial. Many choose to use the more clandestine bio-system augmentations that keep them looking mostly human except for the odd piece here and there, such as a sensor antenna or mechanical eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tor Rayean</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tor_rayean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tor_rayean/</guid>
      <description>title: Tor Rayean desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Tor_Rayean percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Tor Rayean Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Runner Date of Birth: Height: 6&amp;rsquo; Weight: 185lbs Hair Color: Black Eye Color: Brown Physical Description: Tor is of medium height and build, with dark eyes and generally greasy hair. He does little in the way of making himself pallatable to anyone and is the sort of person that most other folks instinctively give a wide berth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turin Glastnost</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/turin_glastnost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/turin_glastnost/</guid>
      <description>title: Turin Glastnost desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Turin_Glastnost percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Turin Glastnost Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Psychic/Criminal Mastermind Date of Birth: January 1, 2999 Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo; Weight: 190lbs Hair Color: Dark Brown Eye Color: Dark Hazel Physical Description: Turin is an amazing physical specimine, with dark hair, dark eyes, a fit body, and a poise and confidence born from a lifetime of successes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincent Torres</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/vincent_torres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/vincent_torres/</guid>
      <description>title: Vincent Torres desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Vincent_Torres percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Vincent (Vin) Mathew Torres Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Pilot/Runner, runs a small charter/cargo business out of Earth Station Date of Birth: October 3, 3012 Height: 6&amp;rsquo;4&amp;rdquo; Weight: 210lbs Hair Color: Blond Eye Color: Blue Physical Description:
General Description Vincent is tall, athletic, and charismatic. He loves the small pleasures in life and does not play by other people&amp;rsquo;s rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayne Nelson</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/wayne_nelson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/wayne_nelson/</guid>
      <description>title: Wayne Nelson desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Wayne_Nelson percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Wayne Edward Nelson Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: Cybernetic Engineer Date of Birth: July 21, 2998 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;2&amp;rdquo; Weight: 110lbs Hair Color: Black Eye Color: Hazel Green Physical Description: Wayne is an extremely short man with a balled crown surrounded by wispy dark hair and a goblin-like face with a long pointed nose and protruding eyebrow ridges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Willhelmina Orlova</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/willhelmina_orlova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/willhelmina_orlova/</guid>
      <description>title: Willhelmina Orlova desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Willhelmina_Orlova percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Willhelmina Katarina Orlova Aliases: Avatar/Player: Katrina Annwyn Thorindal Occupation: Courier for Solidarity Online Date of Birth: April 28, 3011 Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo; Weight: 130lbs Hair Color: Black Eye Color: Emerald Green Physical Description:
General Description Willhelmina is a twenty-four year old woman who has spent more than half of her life almost continuously connected to Kalijor, in order to keep the character of Katrina as real as possible to Riana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Quinn</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/xavier_quinn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/xavier_quinn/</guid>
      <description>title: Xavier Quinn desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Xavier_Quinn percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Full Name: Xavier David Quinn Aliases: Avatar/Player: Occupation: CEO, Solidarity Online Date of Birth: 2992 Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo; Weight: 211lbs Hair Color: Black Eye Color: Grey Physical Description: He stands just over six feet tall and has dark hair that falls to the middle of his back and is always restrained in a pony tail and very well maintained, never a single strand out of place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>