<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weapons of the Future on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weapons of the Future on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>10Mm Handgun</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_handgun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_handgun/</guid>
      <description>The 10mm caseless round is the standard amunition for most weapons in the Sol system, including law enforcement and military personnel. The auto-pistol favored by most spec-ops personnel has a standard 15 round magazine and selective firing modes of safe, semi-automatic (one round per trigger pull), burst (three rounds per trigger pull), and full automatic (fires for as long as the trigger is held down). There is also a 30 round extended magazine for the weapon that will extend full-auto firing time but unbalances the weapon slightly and makes it more difficult to conceal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10Mm Sub Machine Gun</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_sub_machine_gun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_sub_machine_gun/</guid>
      <description>The 10mm caseless round is the standard amunition for most weapons in the Sol system including law enforcement and military weapons. Most sub-machine guns used by spec-ops personnel have a standard 30 round magazine and selective firing modes of safe, semi-automatic (one round per trigger pull), burst (three rounds per trigger pull), and full automatic (fires for as long as the trigger is held down). These weapons are extremely reliable, easy to clean and fire in all environments and conditions including the vacuum of space (The shaped charge propellant is oxygen impregnated so that it has everything needed to fire in any environment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash Bang</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/flash-bang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/flash-bang/</guid>
      <description>Flash-bangs are a particular type of grenade that are used by law enforcement for the specific purpose of crowd control in enclosed areas. A flash-bang, when triggered, will release an extremely loud, deafening noise, along with a blinding pulse of light. Together these two effects will stun and disorient the people near the point of the detonation.
Range: About 40 to 100 feet when thrown by an average person. Can be upwards of 250 feet when thrown by someone with cybernetic/genetic augmentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grenade</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/grenade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/grenade/</guid>
      <description>Grenades come in a myriad of forms and functions, from simple explosives to fragmentation grenades, to much more advanced concussion, soni,c and even chemical grenades, if non-lethal options are preferred.
The basic technology is easy for even the untrained to operate, simply pull the pin/press the button and throw the device toward the target. Most operate on extremely reliable solid-state electronic timers and on some of the higher end devices the timer can be adjusted to any length of time required by the user, or even set to detonate on impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand To Hand Classifications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/hand_to_hand_classifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/hand_to_hand_classifications/</guid>
      <description>Class 1 These individuals are the top echelon of martial arts experts. They have dedicated their entire lives to the study of the martial arts and associated philosophies. Class 1 combatants are typically fifth degree or higher black belts in two or more styles and have studied extensively in multiple additional forms of martial arts. Through decades of devotion and constant practice they have become masters of their art, although they still constantly seek to hone their skills and develop new techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Frequency Blade</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/high-frequency_blade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/high-frequency_blade/</guid>
      <description>High frequency blades are a new twist on an old standard. They are basically swords and knives made of high strength alloys. Well balanced weapons with keen cutting edges that are then enhanced by the addition of a high-frequency reciprocating motor that causes the blade to vibrate almost beyond the range of human perception. The end result is a bladed weapon that cuts much like a chain saw. These blades are able to cut through most materials including metal alloys as strong as starship hull plating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/laser/</guid>
      <description>Light Amplification through the Stimulated Emission of Radiation. Lasers have been around for a long, long time, and over the years they have been continually refined, adjusted, and tweaked until they finally became more than simple communications and entertainment tools.
Since the days of the first laser satellite defense systems the technology has advanced with increasing speed. Basically nothing more than a coherent beam of light at a single, controllable, frequency/wavelength, it was always known that they could be used as weapons, but the big question at hand was always, how do we provide enough energy in a small enough package to make them practical and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monomolecular Blade</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/monomolecular_blade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/monomolecular_blade/</guid>
      <description>The monomolecular sword or knife is an extremely expensive, and dangerous alternative to the standard swords and knives that have been around for centuries.
The basic idea is still the same however. To make a melee weapon that is as sharp as you can possibly make it and will, in the hands of the correct wielder, be an extremely effective weapon. In the case of these weapons there is a wire or filament that is formed from a super dense alloy (although really almost any substance will work as long as it is ferrous).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Particle Beam</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/particle_beam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/particle_beam/</guid>
      <description>Particle beams are weapons that accelerate atomic or sub-atomic particles to within a few percent of the speed of light and then direct them at a target through a series of electrostatic (not electromagnetic) focusing/acceleration arrays. Essentially they are very similar to rail guns or electromagnetic mass drivers except that they use electrostatic forces rather than electromagnetic, and they are firing beams of particles rather than solid slugs or projectiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weapon Classifications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/weapon_classifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/weapon_classifications/</guid>
      <description>Weapons are broken down into classes based upon several factors. Range, Ammunition type (where applicable), damage potential versus organic materials (people), Damage potential versus inorganic materials (structures and vehicles), Weight, and Legality.
Class A Class A weapons are weapons with limited or no range, blunt or sharp edges designed to cause damage through various forms of bashing, smashing, slicing, chopping, piercing, etc. Examples of Class A weapons would include Swords, Staves, Axes, Knives, Maces, Clubs, Cudgels, Spears, Pole-arms and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>