<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology of the Future on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology of the Future on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Gravity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/artificial_gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/artificial_gravity/</guid>
      <description>Artificial gravity is created, in most cases, by placing a disk made of super-conducting material inside a sealed environment. The disk is suspended within a magnetic field so that it can not touch any portion of its casing, and then spun at extreme velocities (Approximately 130,000 RPM). This creates a gravito-magnetic field that extends outward from the device in a 100 ft radius. For most small craft, one or two generators is usually enough to create approximately 1G (Earth normal) of gravitational force throughout the entire vessel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body Armor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/body_armor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/body_armor/</guid>
      <description>Personal protective body armor comes in a variety of shapes, styles and materials, most of which are designed for specific conditions, or to protect against specific forms of damage. For the purposes of simplicity, the records here are broken down into categories describing the physical composition or properties of the armor type in question, such as soft, or hard, etc.
Soft Armor is usually composed of some type of synthetic material that is woven in numerous layers that are designed to spread out the kinetic force of incoming projectiles, thereby reducing the amount of penetrative force or damage said projectile is capable of inflicting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/communications/</guid>
      <description>The standard communication medium of the day has become sub-space. Sub-space is mathematically defined as an infinite space that exists within our realm inside a finite boundary. It was discovered in the past 300 years that in any given sub-space realm there is a direct correlation between each point in that realm and each point within our own. However, energy behaves differently within any given sub-space realm than it does within normal-space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computers</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/computers/</guid>
      <description>Over centuries of development, computer technology has continued to grow and evolve. After the industry maxed out the capabilities of standard semi-conductor chips they moved on to super-conducting materials and then to the inevitable optical systems, allowing computers to operate at relativistic speeds. Today&amp;rsquo;s computers are all optical processing units that operate on a hexadecimal base programming system. Moving away from a binary base language allows developers to represent significantly more complicated concepts and data with much smaller amounts of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybernetics</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/cybernetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/cybernetics/</guid>
      <description>Cybernetics is the science of replacing normal biological parts with artificial ones that fill the same roll. In the beginning of the 20th century it began with pace-makers and artificial hearts and from there developed at a break-neck pace until before long any organ in the human body, with the exception of the spine and brain, could be easily replaced with an artificial equivalent. Once joints, bones, and even muscle tissue began to be effectively replaced and the ties into the nervous system became more reliable and faster, it did not take a fantastic leap of creativity to begin using this science to actually augment the parts in question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Shields</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/energy_shields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/energy_shields/</guid>
      <description>Energy shields come in a couple of different forms. The earliest forms of energy shielding for space craft were nothing more than sophisticated tracking algorithms designed to track incoming debris and then vaporize it with a ship&amp;rsquo;s weapon systems. This system proved to be effective, however costly in terms of computer power, sensor usage, and energy consumption. These systems were adept at eliminating space debris and small particles but proved ineffectual at handling most incoming weapons fire and extremely small matter such as micro-meteorites that could still cause significant damage to a space vessel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/interstellar_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/interstellar_travel/</guid>
      <description>Super-Luminal propulsion is a relatively new science as far as practical application is concerned. There are currently two very different technologies in use by space craft. Gravitic drives, and Traction drives.
Gravitic drives harness the power of gravity to propel a space craft faster than the speed of light. By focusing a beam of focused gravitons, the craft is able to push itself away from solid matter with great force. Initially gravitic drives only worked while in relative close proximity to large celestial bodies such as stars and planets, but as the technology was refined it became less dependant on such ‘anchor points’ and is now capable of propelling itself through open space by repelling its graviton beam off of free roaming particles in space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intrastellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/intrastellar_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/intrastellar_travel/</guid>
      <description>Chemical
Nuclear/Anti-Matter
Solar
Ion/Plasma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riana&#39;S Body</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/rianas_body/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/rianas_body/</guid>
      <description>Riana’s cybernetic body is arguably a product of the most advanced and forward thinking technology known to mankind. It is designed to almost perfectly mimic a normal human body in nearly every way as far as construction and structure are concerned, but enhances, strengthens, and builds upon that construction and form immeasurably. Her skeleton is composed of a carbon-carbon honeycomb that is laced/reinforced and sheathed in 6.6.2 Titanium. This makes her bones both extremely light, and incredibly resilient to breaking, shattering and other forms of damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft Technology</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/spacecraft_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/spacecraft_technology/</guid>
      <description>Space craft are now fairly commonplace with models available for prices that the upper middle class can begin to afford. Space travel is still not tightly regulated in open space, although flying in or near an inhabited body (Meaning planet, moon, asteroid, space station, etc) requires a pilot’s license and all of the appropriate clearances from ground control for the air-space in question.
There are a myriad of different types and designs of space craft available, ranging from sleek, sexy two-seaters to family size six to ten passenger ships, then up into cargo hauling and mobile home sized vessels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weapon Technology</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/weapon_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/weapon_technology/</guid>
      <description>With all of the advances in technology that seem to permeate the everyday lives of the citizens of the Sol System it is often asked, why are there not more advanced weapons in use? The answers are myriad and varied depending upon whom you are speaking to, however there are a few that are commonly cited, and ring true. To begin with, are there more advanced personal weapons available? Absolutely. Examples of which follow this article for those that are curious for more information but include briefly, coherent light energy weapons or lasers, charged particle weapons, or particle beams, ionizing gas discharge or plasma weapons, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>