<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 21:52:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Author</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/about/author/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 12:10:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/about/author/</guid>
      <description>My name is Paul Lell. I grew up in and around Arvada, Colorado (excepting a two year stint in Kansas because of my father&amp;rsquo;s work). I attended Arvada West High School, graduating in 1992. In 1994 I moved to Pueblo, Colorado where I spent five years attending the educational institute formerly known as the University of Southern Colorado. I started off as an engineering major (leaning toward civil engineering) until one day in the middle of an advanced trigonometry class I had a sudden epiphany: I no longer enjoyed doing math.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalijor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/about/kalijor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 12:11:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/about/kalijor/</guid>
      <description>Kalijor is the product of a lot of dreaming, a lot of hard work, and a lot of fun times. I conceived the world of Kalijor after nearly ten years of role playing with my friends through school. I loved the games we played but I quickly grew tired of trying to fit my own ideas inside the framework of the world settings that the source books offered. That and I wanted to have a better reason to tell my friends that they couldn&amp;rsquo;t play that uber evil-smashing mega knight deluxe character, and setting them in my own world with specifically allowable character types seemed the best way to go and make everyone fall in with a minimum of fuss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalijor.com</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/about/kalijor-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 12:11:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/about/kalijor-com/</guid>
      <description>This web site was born of two very different needs. The first was to get the information about the book, sales, author and so forth out to you the people. Thus the primary page and associated links (this page included). The second need was to get out as much information about Kalijor as I possibly can. Kalijor is HUGE. MUCH larger than my novels will likely ever be able to encompass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/_footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/_footer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/_header/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/_header/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10Mm Handgun</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_handgun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_handgun/</guid>
      <description>The 10mm caseless round is the standard amunition for most weapons in the Sol system, including law enforcement and military personnel. The auto-pistol favored by most spec-ops personnel has a standard 15 round magazine and selective firing modes of safe, semi-automatic (one round per trigger pull), burst (three rounds per trigger pull), and full automatic (fires for as long as the trigger is held down). There is also a 30 round extended magazine for the weapon that will extend full-auto firing time but unbalances the weapon slightly and makes it more difficult to conceal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10Mm Sub Machine Gun</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_sub_machine_gun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/10mm_sub_machine_gun/</guid>
      <description>The 10mm caseless round is the standard amunition for most weapons in the Sol system including law enforcement and military weapons. Most sub-machine guns used by spec-ops personnel have a standard 30 round magazine and selective firing modes of safe, semi-automatic (one round per trigger pull), burst (three rounds per trigger pull), and full automatic (fires for as long as the trigger is held down). These weapons are extremely reliable, easy to clean and fire in all environments and conditions including the vacuum of space (The shaped charge propellant is oxygen impregnated so that it has everything needed to fire in any environment).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achilles</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/achilles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/achilles/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Achilles
Other Names:
Location: Mars (Equitorial region)
Permanent Population: Around eight million
Transient Population: 500,000 to 750,000 mostly to accommodate work crews for the Valles Marineris project
Imports: Food, medical supplies, entertainment
Exports: Manufactured goods of all kinds from small appliances through toys and sub-components for larger systems such as starships and their supporting systems.
Description One of the major Martian cities, Achilles is located near the western edge of the Valles Marineris, a three-thousand mile long, mile deep trench that hugs the planet’s equator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aegis Online</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/aegis_online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/aegis_online/</guid>
      <description>One of the five corporations that make up The Conglomerate. Aegis Online is a firm that is almost entirely dedicated to the creation of MMO’s and the technology associated with them. They are one of the major innovators in the computer technology field, constantly striving to push technology to the next level in order to support the next iteration of their MMO’s. On the software front they are highly regarded as one of the very best programming firms in the Sol system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alina Martin</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/alina_martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/alina_martin/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Alina Martin
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Independant Operator
Date of Birth: February 23, 3015
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;10&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 140 lbs
Hair Color: Green
Eye Color: Bright Green
Physical Description: Alina Martin has a runner&amp;rsquo;s body, which she works regularly to maintain. Her naturally bright green eyes come from her father&amp;rsquo;s side of the family, and when she graduated high school, she purchased gene-therapy to change her hair color to match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Almon Genloe</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/almon_genloe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/almon_genloe/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Almon Genloe
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Crime Lord
Date of Birth: October 18, 2990
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 200 lbs
Hair Color: Dark Brown
Eye Color: Grey
Physical Description:
General Description Almon is a discerning businessman, with a pronounced ability to keep business, pleasure, and personal life, all in their own separate compartments. He dresses like a millionaire (which he is, several times over), treates his employees with respect, and his enemies, even more so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ambrai Valkyrie</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/ambrai_valkyrie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/ambrai_valkyrie/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Ambrai Valkyrie
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Ranger
Date of Birth: 148 years old
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;10&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 125lbs
Hair Color: Fiery Red
Eye Color: Green
Physical Description:
General Description Young and full of vibrant energy and lust for life, Ambrai was a Ranger of accomplished skill with both the bow and the sword. She led a group of adventurers for many years and was the best of friends with each and every one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anja Reyals</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/anja_reyals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/anja_reyals/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Anja Reyals Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Unknown
Date of Birth: Unknown
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 350lbs (looks around 125lbs)
Hair Color: Icy Blue
Eye Color: Cobalt Blue
Physical Description: Anja looks to have an athletic build, despite her weight which is caused by her unique body. She has long, tapered ears, light blue eyes and dark blue hair that, when unrestrained, reaches the small of her back. With the exception of her eye and hair color, and the absence of any tattoos she is an exact physical copy of Riana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annwyn Thorindal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/annwyn_thorindal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/annwyn_thorindal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Annwyn Thorindal
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Mage
Date of Birth: 2075 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 140lbs
Hair Color: Platinum Blond
Eye Color: Violet
Physical Description: Slim, elegant, and refined. The consummate elf. Annwyn was an accomplished mage and a loving mother.
General Description Skills of Note Equipment of Note History After Kilishandra was born and Wyndel seemed to go mad, Annwyn stole away from him and raised Kilishandra within the protective walls of Cohai until she was old enough to attend the Magic Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/april/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: APRIL (Actualized Personal Relativistic Intelligence Link)
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Pincher, personal support for Daray Bowen
Date of Birth: January 1, 3047
Height: NA (About 6 feet in cyberspace)
Weight: NA (Looks to weigh about 120 pounds in cyberspace)
Hair Color: NA (Glowing yellow in cyberspace)
Eye Color: NA (Glowing green in cyberspace)
Physical Description: While cyberjacking APRIL appears as a six foot tall, athleticly built, glowing female with flowing, gravity-defying hair down to her waist and glowing green eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arc Ships</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/arc_ships/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/arc_ships/</guid>
      <description>These massive vessels were built to send humanity out into the stars before the advent of super-luminal drive technology.
Arc-Ships were designed to house tens of thousands of people, have facilities to grow food and recycle waste, and otherwise be completely enclosed, self-sustaining ecosystems. They left earth with crews numbering in the thousands, and were intended to travel to the closest stars to Sol that had been determined to have Earth-type planetoids orbiting them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Gravity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/artificial_gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/artificial_gravity/</guid>
      <description>Artificial gravity is created, in most cases, by placing a disk made of super-conducting material inside a sealed environment. The disk is suspended within a magnetic field so that it can not touch any portion of its casing, and then spun at extreme velocities (Approximately 130,000 RPM). This creates a gravito-magnetic field that extends outward from the device in a 100 ft radius. For most small craft, one or two generators is usually enough to create approximately 1G (Earth normal) of gravitational force throughout the entire vessel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid Belt</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/asteroid_belt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/asteroid_belt/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: The Asteroid Belt
Other Names: The Belt, or Beltway
Location: Between Jupiter and Saturn
Permanent Population: Around three million people.
Transient Population: 100-5,000
Imports: Everything but food.
Exports: The Belt is the Sol system’s primary source of raw metals and other hard construction materials.
Description ‘The Belt’ refers to the community that lives and works in the asteroid belt that lay between Jupiter and Saturn. As such, it is not really a physical location, so much as a a series of cobbled-together space stations/habitats amongst the asteroids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avian</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/avian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/avian/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Avian
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Avian is the home of the bird races of Kalijor. The city is nestled into three tiers that are composed of the tightly intertwined branches of a miles high petrified tree on the southern apex of the Uraval Mountains . The tiers of the city each represent a class of people, with the lowest tier being home to the lower class laborers, shops, artisans and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bartholomew (Bart) Jankoweitz</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/bartholomew_bart_jankoweitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/bartholomew_bart_jankoweitz/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Bartholomew (Bart) Jankoweitz
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Neuro-Psychologist
Date of Birth: April 7, 3012
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 185lbs
Hair Color: Sandy Blond
Eye Color: Icy Blue
Physical Description: He is a tall man with sandy blond hair, fair skin and icy blue eyes. He is outgoing, very personable and gets very excited about new and interesting things concerning people’s brains and how they react to stimuli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Base Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/base-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/base-line/</guid>
      <description>Base-line Humans are people that have less than 10% cybernetic parts (not counting cosmetic alterations that are easily removed) or less than 1% genetic alterations. These people are about as regular as is possible with no real special abilities or powers to speak of. Base-line humans make up the majority by far, more than 90% of the known population of the Sol system).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beier Ikhaya</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/beier_ikhaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/beier_ikhaya/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Beier Ikhaya
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Features/Places of Note Government History Spoilers Status:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body Armor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/body_armor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/body_armor/</guid>
      <description>Personal protective body armor comes in a variety of shapes, styles and materials, most of which are designed for specific conditions, or to protect against specific forms of damage. For the purposes of simplicity, the records here are broken down into categories describing the physical composition or properties of the armor type in question, such as soft, or hard, etc.
Soft Armor is usually composed of some type of synthetic material that is woven in numerous layers that are designed to spread out the kinetic force of incoming projectiles, thereby reducing the amount of penetrative force or damage said projectile is capable of inflicting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning Expanse</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/burning_expanse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/burning_expanse/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: The Burning Expanse
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Burning Expanse is a vast, flat, wasteland of scorching sand and heat. There is no water in the Burning Expanse save for a small oasis that is surrounded by high, impassable cliffs in the southeastern corner of the area. There are no roads here, no cities, no homes, and definitely no guards or patrols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bête Noire</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/b%C3%AAte_noire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/b%C3%AAte_noire/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Bête Noire
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The city of Bête Noire is located on the dark side of Kalijor, in the shadow of a mostly inactive volcano that bears the same name.
Bête Noire is a city rivaling Rathalon in size and population, partially because it is one of the only major cities in the world that allows sentients to get away with some of the darker things in life, namely thievery, scamming, prostitution, and the occasional &amp;lsquo;accidental&amp;rsquo; death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ceres</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/ceres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/ceres/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Ceres
Other Names: The Dregs
Location: The Primary Asteroid Belt (between Jupiter and Saturn)
Permanent Population: Fifty million
Transient Population: 500,000 to one million
Imports: Mostly consumer products and finer goods that are luxury items not produced locally.
Exports: A variety of raw materials and sub-components for starcraft, weapons, and facilities of all kinds.
Description The largest of the planetoids in the Asteroid Belt and home to more than fifty million people and families who choose to live &amp;lsquo;off the grid&amp;rsquo; as disidents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chavan</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/chavan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/chavan/</guid>
      <description>Chavan is the staff given to Katrina Thorindal by Dorin. It is forged of a rare earth metal alloy that makes it lighter than most wooden staves and stronger than most tempered metals. In addition, Dorin imbued the staff with several magical abilities as he forged it. It is a light grey in color and covered from tip to tip in dwarvish runes that make no coherent sense. It’s unique powers include the ability for the staff to create a small pool of cool, pure drinking water by leaving it laying prone on the ground for a moment, the ability to attract small game animals by stabbing the staff into the ground and letting it stand for a few moments, and the ability to cast a steady, white light, of similar intensity to a high quality torch by tapping one of its ends against the ground several times repeatedly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cohai Observatory</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/cohai_observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/cohai_observatory/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Cohai Observatory
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Cohai Observatory is a keep that sits at the top of a spire of rock that thrusts up some three or four thousand feet from the western face of the Uraval Mountains . The only land based approach to Cohai is from a narrow pass in the Forest of Brume that leads to an ancient rope bridge spanning the two-hundred foot gap from the mountains to the spire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Fusion</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/cold_fusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/cold_fusion/</guid>
      <description>One of the five corporations that make up The Conglomerate. Cold Fusion began life as a nuclear fusion research organization that, through the years, evolved into various forms of production and other research. Their insights into fusion power cells allowed them to quickly dominate the mobile technology market and most mobile devices still use their power cells (or power cells based upon their original designs) to this day. The Cold Fusion corporation practices business honorably, but they treat other corporate entities as they are treated by them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/communications/</guid>
      <description>The standard communication medium of the day has become sub-space. Sub-space is mathematically defined as an infinite space that exists within our realm inside a finite boundary. It was discovered in the past 300 years that in any given sub-space realm there is a direct correlation between each point in that realm and each point within our own. However, energy behaves differently within any given sub-space realm than it does within normal-space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computers</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/computers/</guid>
      <description>Over centuries of development, computer technology has continued to grow and evolve. After the industry maxed out the capabilities of standard semi-conductor chips they moved on to super-conducting materials and then to the inevitable optical systems, allowing computers to operate at relativistic speeds. Today&amp;rsquo;s computers are all optical processing units that operate on a hexadecimal base programming system. Moving away from a binary base language allows developers to represent significantly more complicated concepts and data with much smaller amounts of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybernetics</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/cybernetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/cybernetics/</guid>
      <description>Cybernetics is the science of replacing normal biological parts with artificial ones that fill the same roll. In the beginning of the 20th century it began with pace-makers and artificial hearts and from there developed at a break-neck pace until before long any organ in the human body, with the exception of the spine and brain, could be easily replaced with an artificial equivalent. Once joints, bones, and even muscle tissue began to be effectively replaced and the ties into the nervous system became more reliable and faster, it did not take a fantastic leap of creativity to begin using this science to actually augment the parts in question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daray (Dare) Bowen</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/daray_dare_bowen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/daray_dare_bowen/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Daray (Dare) Bowen Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Pincher (corporate espionage expert)
Date of Birth: July 18, 3047
Height: 4’9”
Weight: 118 lbs (looks like she couldn’t weigh more than 90 lbs)
Hair Color: Strawberry Blonde
Eye Color: Dark Cobalt Blue
Physical Description: Short and almost scary thin, Daray is actually a lot tougher than she seems. She has a look about her that is at once very pleasing to the eye and at the same time engineered to fade quickly from memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daray&#39;s Penthouse</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/darays_penthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/darays_penthouse/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Daray&amp;rsquo;s Penthouse
Other Names: Home
Location: Tranquility, Luna
Permanent Population: 2
Transient Population: A dozen or so, depending upon the day and what&amp;rsquo;s going on.
Imports: Food, goods, friends, weapons, ammunition&amp;hellip;
Exports: A constant sense of wonder and lust for life.
Description Originally purchased and furnished by Solidarity Online for use as housing for agents on assignment or in need of a safe house. Daray was given use of the home and its facilities when Xavier sent her to Tranquility to get to the bottom of the Aegis Online plan to kill or lobotomize millions of Kalijor players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Darren Owen Erricson</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/darren_owen_erricson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/darren_owen_erricson/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Darren Owen Erricson Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Private Courier
Date of Birth: December 25, 3027
Height: 6’4”
Weight: 180 lbs
Hair Color: Dark Brown
Eye Color: Hazel-green
Physical Description: Physically Darren is in amazing shape. He has the toned body of a tri-athlete due to his regularly Parkouring around the Venus Station. He keeps his dark brown hair short and manageable so that he can be up and about, and looking his best, at a moment’s notice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Sea</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/dead_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/dead_sea/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Dead Sea
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Dead Sea is a large, rancid body of sickly, thick, green water that rests in the southern end of the Plain of Sorrow. This sea was once a life spring before it was corrupted by some unknown force that destroyed it and the ancient forest surrounding it.
Nothing living resides in the Dead Sea, although several demons and undead creatures make their homes beneath its toxic waters, venturing out only to seek fresh souls to feed their ravenous appetites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Destra</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/destra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/destra/</guid>
      <description>Destra is the wicked, black sword wielded by Malice. It is a sword of similar dimensions to a bastard sword, although a touch longer. Destra was forged in a magical fire by a dwarven smith and quenched in the blood of innocents killed by ritual sacrifice. The sword is coal black from tip to handle, it&amp;rsquo;s only mark of color being a deep, navy blue sapphire set into the pommel of the weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digerati</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/digerati/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/digerati/</guid>
      <description>Digerati are the elite computer hackers and programmers who move through the net as if it were their own personal play space. True Digerati, not just elite (or claiming to be elite) hackers can move through computer systems, bypassing firewalls and other security measures with little to no effort. These cyber samurai tend to operate on a strict moral code that may make sense to nobody but themselves, but they stick to it no matter what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinendal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/dinendal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/dinendal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Dinendal
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Master Tattoo Artisan
Date of Birth: 452 years old
Height: 3&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 150lbs
Hair Color: Coal Black
Eye Color: Brown
Physical Description:
General Description Dinendal is your typical Dwarf. Outgoing, beligerant, and fun at parties. He is a master of his craft and highly sought after for body work in Kalijor.
The Master Dwarven artisan that applied Riana’s tattoos. His shop is in Talanor and he is renowned throughout Kalijor as one of the best artisans in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissidents</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/dissidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/dissidents/</guid>
      <description>Any person or persons who have either chosen, or have been forced to live &amp;lsquo;off the grid&amp;rsquo;. These people are not citizens of The Conglomerate and are treated as lower than second-class people by any Conglomerate personnel who may encounter them. It is technically illegal for Dissidents to enter, leave, or simpley be, inside any Conglomerate facility or vessel. Dissidents have no rights, no privelages, and are unable to own property, have jobs, spend money, or interact with Conglomerate citizens in any way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dorin</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/dorin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/dorin/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Dorin
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Cook/Blacksmith
Date of Birth: 525 years old
Height: 3&amp;rsquo;6&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 148lbs
Hair Color: Dark Brown
Eye Color: Green
Physical Description: He is an average sized Dwarf with long dark colored hair and beard that are fairly well kept, and smiling, dark eyes. He has a round, almost bulbous nose, and is a bit on the weak side as dwarves go, hardly able to lift three times his own weight in stone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dregs</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/dregs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/dregs/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: The Dregs
Other Names:
Location: The Asteroid Belt (between Jupiter and Saturn)
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports: Nothing critical. Mostly luxury items and goods that are not produced locally.
Exports: Officially, Nothing. Unofficially, the Dregs is the largest producer of starship components, sensory systems, drives, and habitate modules/components in the solar system.
Description The term ‘The Dregs’ does not refer to any place in particular but rather everything not covered specifically elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dwarf</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/dwarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/dwarf/</guid>
      <description>Dwarves are a subterranean race that are intelligent, belligerent, and extremely capable builders and excavators. As a rule, dwarves make excellent craftsmen and artisans, some of the finest weapons and armor in Kalijor have been credited back to dwarven craftsmen. Dwarves and elves tend not to get along very well due to some ancient hostility between their two peoples, although not openly combative under normal circumstances, it takes very little coaxing to get a dwarf to into a confrontation with an elf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/earth/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Earth
Other Names: Mother Earth, The Cradel of Human civilization
Location: Third Rock from the Sun
Permanent Population: 0
Transient Population: 0
Imports: Nothing
Exports: Nothing
Description The cradle of human civilization. The blue-green gem in the night sky of every other world or station in the Sol system. Over five-hundred years ago the human race made a valiant attempt at destroying itself with the aid of nuclear fission and nuclear fusion weapons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Ring Station</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/earth_ring_station/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/earth_ring_station/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: The Earth Ring Station
Other Names: Ring Station, &amp;lsquo;Earth&amp;rsquo;
Location: Built in geo-synchronous orbit around Earth
Permanent Population: 5 billion
Transient Population: 10 million to 100 million souls
Imports: Food, Raw materials both organic and non-organic, prefabricated starship components, entertainment.
Exports: Medical supplies, Weapons, Starships (both sub-luminal and super-luminal).
Description It consists of three massive rings that intersect at perpendicular angles to one another, perfectly quartering the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/elf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/elf/</guid>
      <description>Elves are an elegant, intelligent, and prideful people. They are the masters of whatever they undertake, always striving to be without peer. It is this attitude which is said to have led to the great war millennia ago when elven and dwarven craftsmen were driven to war over the subject of who’s skills where the better when it came to forging magical weapons. Since that war the elves have almost entirely given up the art of metal working, preferring instead to devote themselves to nature, magic and wood working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elkorine</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/elkorine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/elkorine/</guid>
      <description>Elkorine is a short sword that was forged by the elves that would later become known as the enigmatic Obscuri, long before the great wars. The sword has been carried by many individuals throughout its life, almost all of whom have become notable in some regard or other. The weapon has a tendency to turn up in the hands of the less likely people in history and is said to have a mind of its own, although no one can recall or find evidence of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emil Frederick, Phd</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/emil_frederick_phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/emil_frederick_phd/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Emil Frederick, PHD
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Bio-Engineer/Doctor of Genetic Sciences
Date of Birth: November 3, 2993
Height: 6 feet, 1 inch
Weight: 190 pounds
Hair Color: Dark brown, peppered with grey
Eye Color: Bright hazel-green
Physical Description: Doctor Emil Frederick is medium height and slightly overweight build, but not unhealthily so. He has bright, intelligent eyes, and a calm, caring demeanor. He dresses comfortably and ususally covers his attire with a long white lab coat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Shields</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/energy_shields/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/energy_shields/</guid>
      <description>Energy shields come in a couple of different forms. The earliest forms of energy shielding for space craft were nothing more than sophisticated tracking algorithms designed to track incoming debris and then vaporize it with a ship&amp;rsquo;s weapon systems. This system proved to be effective, however costly in terms of computer power, sensor usage, and energy consumption. These systems were adept at eliminating space debris and small particles but proved ineffectual at handling most incoming weapons fire and extremely small matter such as micro-meteorites that could still cause significant damage to a space vessel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equun Draco</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/equun-draco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/equun-draco/</guid>
      <description>This creature is a strange cross between a dragon and a horse. Their legs are strong and thick with muscles with clawed toes in any number from two to five. They have long necks, usually about the same length as their body, that are very flexible and fully articulate. They have long, whip-like tails that are anywhere from two to three times the length of their bodies and end in some form of bone blade, or club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exodus</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/exodus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/exodus/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Exodus
Aliases:
Avatar/Player: Jax Arianas
Occupation: Mage (Teleportation/Travel specialty)
Date of Birth: 35 years old
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 180lbs
Hair Color: None (Dark Brown Mustache)
Eye Color: Light Grey
Physical Description: He has a bald head and a well kept mustache that merges into an equally well managed beard of dark brown whiskers. His eyes are a clear, light-grey color and he is normally very calm and collected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezrina Reyals Thorindal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/ezrina_reyals-thorindal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/ezrina_reyals-thorindal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Ezrina Reyals-Thorindal
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Mage/Mother, Self exiled princess of Pandoria
Date of Birth: 850 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;
Weight: 125lbs
Hair Color: Metallic Platinum
Eye Color: Golden Yellow
Physical Description:
General Description On the short side for a royal elf, Ezrina is an extremely adept mage with power enough that some think she has drawn the attention of the Obscuri. She is quiet and thoughtful most of the time but can be a bit bi-polar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felinoid</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/felinoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/felinoid/</guid>
      <description>Felinoids appear to be a combination of cats and humans. They are covered in fur, which is typically short and soft although some have had coarse or long fur, from head to toe. They have pointed, articulated ears, whiskers, slitted pupils, a keen sense of smell and retractable claws in their fingers and toes. Most felinoids have tails and their coloring and patterning ranges all over the place, some following similar designs as typical big game cats, others more like the more domesticated house cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash Bang</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/flash-bang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/flash-bang/</guid>
      <description>Flash-bangs are a particular type of grenade that are used by law enforcement for the specific purpose of crowd control in enclosed areas. A flash-bang, when triggered, will release an extremely loud, deafening noise, along with a blinding pulse of light. Together these two effects will stun and disorient the people near the point of the detonation.
Range: About 40 to 100 feet when thrown by an average person. Can be upwards of 250 feet when thrown by someone with cybernetic/genetic augmentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forest Of Brume</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/forest_of_brume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/forest_of_brume/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Forest of Brume
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Forest of Brume is an ancient forest that dominates more than a third of the light side of Kalijor. It rests between the Northern and Southern Planes of Serenity, runs up to the Uraval Mountains on the east side and the Great Sea to the west. In the center of the forest rests the Great Inland Sea, a body of water that would take a week to cross in any direction and in the center of which is an island where one of the five ziggurats of Kalijor rests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gayle Dyson</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gayle_dyson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gayle_dyson/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Gayle Dyson
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Doctor of Genetic Sciences
Date of Birth: October 11, 3005
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;10&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 130lbs
Hair Color: Blond
Eye Color: Steel Grey
Physical Description: Gayle is nearly six feet tall with long blond hair that is nearly always tied back in a tight bun and steely grey eyes. She is not very personable and has a reputation as an ice queen among the men of the posts to which she has been assigned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gelid Mountains</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/gelid_mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/gelid_mountains/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Gelid Mountains
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Gelid Mountains are a range of low mountains that sit between the Southern Wastes and the Northern Wastes. The largest peak in the range is Mount Tellamon, the home of the city of Talanor. The mountains, although low in elevation are frigid cold year round. They are nearly always shrouded in heavy, dark clouds and suffering from constant blizzard conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gene-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gene-line/</guid>
      <description>Gene-line Humans are individuals who have either undergone extensive genetic alteration, or are the offspring of extensively altered individuals. The extent of genetic engineering is almost unlimited and nearly anything is possible, from simply altering the color of a person’s eyes or hair, all the way to rebuilding their body from the ground up to be anything that is desired, from an elf to a minotaur,‘aliens’ and more.
Gene-line humans are by far the most serious threat to anyone trying to establish an understanding of the people they are dealing with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gnome</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/gnome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/gnome/</guid>
      <description>Gnomes are small, generally frail looking individuals that normally live in subterranean locations. They are smaller even than dwarves but seem to share their same brash attitudes, tending to think everyone else is intellectually inferior to them despite any illustrations to the contrary. Gnomes are consummate tinkerers, always trying to invent or improve things in strange new ways. The studious nature of gnomes makes them excellent mages while their small stature makes them a poor choice for physical combat, although such things are not entirely unheard of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goblin</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/goblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/goblin/</guid>
      <description>Goblins are short, hairless humanoids that are particularly clever in the ways of misdirection. They Have long, pointy ears, inky black eyes, and four digits on each hand/foot. Their size ranges from around two feet to nearly four feet and their color is usually some shade of green, although some yellows and greys are not unheard of. Goblins enjoy games of trickery and chance and make excellent thieves.
Average Life Span: 100 to 250 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gornin</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/gornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/gornin/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Gornin
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Teacher
Date of Birth: Unknown
Height: 7&amp;rsquo;2&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 275lbs
Hair Color: None
Eye Color: Blue
Physical Description: Gornin is an unusual troll and the master of the Cohai Observatory. He is about seven feet tall (Average height for a troll), and well muscled. His teeth are abnormally straight for a troll and he has no body hair at all. He has clear, piercing blue eyes, the color of the sea after a storm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Inland Sea</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/great_inland_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/great_inland_sea/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Great Inland Sea
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Great Inland Sea is the largest, land-locked body of water in Kalijor. It is surrounded by the Forest of Brume and on the southern and western shores lay the oldest parts of the forest. This huge body of water is dark and calm, relatively warm and, if you stay close to shore, safe for swimming in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gregory Shantal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gregory_shantal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/gregory_shantal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Gregory Shantal
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation:
Date of Birth: Unknown (Assumed to be in his 70&amp;rsquo;s)
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;3&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 515lbs (looks around 160lbs)
Hair Color: Grey/Silver
Eye Color: Blue
Physical Description:
General Description Gregory Shantal is a mercenary that has earned himself a well deserved reputation as a brutal and efficient soldier. He hires himself out to the highest bidder and does not care what kind of work they ask him to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grenade</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/grenade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/grenade/</guid>
      <description>Grenades come in a myriad of forms and functions, from simple explosives to fragmentation grenades, to much more advanced concussion, soni,c and even chemical grenades, if non-lethal options are preferred.
The basic technology is easy for even the untrained to operate, simply pull the pin/press the button and throw the device toward the target. Most operate on extremely reliable solid-state electronic timers and on some of the higher end devices the timer can be adjusted to any length of time required by the user, or even set to detonate on impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand To Hand Classifications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/hand_to_hand_classifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/hand_to_hand_classifications/</guid>
      <description>Class 1 These individuals are the top echelon of martial arts experts. They have dedicated their entire lives to the study of the martial arts and associated philosophies. Class 1 combatants are typically fifth degree or higher black belts in two or more styles and have studied extensively in multiple additional forms of martial arts. Through decades of devotion and constant practice they have become masters of their art, although they still constantly seek to hone their skills and develop new techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hector</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/hector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/hector/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Hector
Other Names:
Location: Mars, Equitorial Region.
Permanent Population: 5 million
Transient Population:
Imports: Manufactured goods and materials of all kinds.
Exports: Food and medicinal plants and organic components.
Description One of the major Martian cities, Hector is located near the eastern edge of the Valles Marineris, a three-thousand mile long, mile deep trench that hugs the planet’s equator. Near the western edge of the same fissure lies the sister city of Achilles .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Frequency Blade</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/high-frequency_blade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/high-frequency_blade/</guid>
      <description>High frequency blades are a new twist on an old standard. They are basically swords and knives made of high strength alloys. Well balanced weapons with keen cutting edges that are then enhanced by the addition of a high-frequency reciprocating motor that causes the blade to vibrate almost beyond the range of human perception. The end result is a bladed weapon that cuts much like a chain saw. These blades are able to cut through most materials including metal alloys as strong as starship hull plating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/human/</guid>
      <description>Humans are by far the most plentiful race in Kalijor. They range in skin tones from pale white through dark brown, almost ebony. They are an intelligent race that learns quickly but oft times makes rash decisions as they are still quite young, in racial terms. Their life span is short in comparison to the other major races of Kalijor with most living around eighty years although some have lived well into their hundreds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/interstellar_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/interstellar_travel/</guid>
      <description>Super-Luminal propulsion is a relatively new science as far as practical application is concerned. There are currently two very different technologies in use by space craft. Gravitic drives, and Traction drives.
Gravitic drives harness the power of gravity to propel a space craft faster than the speed of light. By focusing a beam of focused gravitons, the craft is able to push itself away from solid matter with great force. Initially gravitic drives only worked while in relative close proximity to large celestial bodies such as stars and planets, but as the technology was refined it became less dependant on such ‘anchor points’ and is now capable of propelling itself through open space by repelling its graviton beam off of free roaming particles in space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intrastellar Travel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/intrastellar_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/intrastellar_travel/</guid>
      <description>Chemical
Nuclear/Anti-Matter
Solar
Ion/Plasma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isle Of Magic</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/isle_of_magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/isle_of_magic/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Isle of Magic
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Isle of magic is located two or three days sail from the Western shores of the Kalijor mainland. This island is where most of the world’s Fay folk have taken up residence in an attempt to remove themselves from the prying eyes of the overly inquisitive races of the world. The geography of the isle varies immensely from area to area, with steep treacherous cliffs dominating the center and an impassible barrier wall completely encircling the island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jax Arianas</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jax_arianas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jax_arianas/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Jax Arianas
Aliases:
Avatar/Player: Exodus
Occupation: Senior Network Security Administrator, Solidarity Online
Date of Birth: August 3, 3009
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;
Weight: 200lbs
Hair Color: Brown
Eye Color: Grey
Physical Description: Jax is about six feet tall with dark hair that he keeps short so as to create a minimum of personal grooming time. He has steel grey eyes and no facial hair. He is fit, but not overly strong as he spends most of his time in Kalijor watching for suspicious activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonin Himabari</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jonin_himabari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/jonin_himabari/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Jonin Himabari
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Martial Arts Instructor for Solidarity Online
Date of Birth: 2985
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;8&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 110lbs
Hair Color: Dark Brown
Eye Color: Brown
Physical Description: He is a smaller man of Asian descent, although he has never discussed his lineage with anyone so his exact parentage is unknown. He is fairly short, light and trim, fit and strong. He has dark hair and dark brown eyes, fine features and is estimated to be around fifty years of age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumah Wataru</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/jumah_wataru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/jumah_wataru/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Jumah Wataru Aliases:
Avatar/Player: Vincent Torres
Occupation: Martial Artist
Date of Birth: 35 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;3&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 225lbs
Hair Color: Blond, with very faint darker spots
Eye Color: Blue
Physical Description: Jumah stands six feet three inches tall in his human form and has a toned, athletic physique, light blond hair that falls to the middle of his back, and deep cobalt blue eyes. His hair has barely discernable darker spots in it and he wears a series of loose braids throughout then ties it all back behind his head to keep it out of the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/jupiter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/jupiter/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Jupiter
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population: Around ten million souls.
Transient Population:
Imports: People, Machinery, Medical supplies, Food.
Exports: Raw materials in the form of gasses and minerals mined from the planet itself and its moons.
Description The Jupiter community is not one single settlement or location but rather numerous bases and stations that reside on the surface of many of the planet’s moons, and in orbit around the planet itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaden Mcginley</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/kaden_mcginley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/kaden_mcginley/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Kaden McGinley
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Runner
Date of Birth:
Height:
Weight:
Hair Color:
Eye Color:
Physical Description:
General Description Friend of Alina Martin and Niko Nori
Skills of Note Equipment of Note History Spoilers Status: Living</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalijor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/kalijor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/kalijor/</guid>
      <description>It is known that before the great war, the elves and dwarves lived in peace and harmony with one another. Their two great people ruled the land with grace, wisdom, and love for the land and all of its offerings. Both races welcomed the younger races into their arms and began to teach them the way of things, magic, art, culture, life. But as is so often the case, nothing lasts forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katrina Annwyn Thorindal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/katrina_annwyn_thorindal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/katrina_annwyn_thorindal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Katrina Annwyn Thorindal Aliases:
Avatar/Player: Willhelmina Orlova
Occupation: Mage
Date of Birth: 38 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 125lbs
Hair Color: Metallic Platinum
Eye Color: Golden Yellow
Physical Description: Physically, Katrina stands just shy of six feet tall and weighs in around one-hundred-ten pounds. She is fit, but spends the majority of her free time with her nose in a book. She has a thin frame and is not weak, but obviously spends very little time exercising.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilishandra Thorindal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/kilishandra_thorindal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/kilishandra_thorindal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Kilishandra Thorindal
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation:
Date of Birth: 291 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 125lbs
Hair Color: Metallic Platinum until the curse turned it a deep red, almost purple.
Eye Color: Violet
Physical Description: Kilishandra was tall for a common elf, she was friendly and outgoing, confident, and intelligent. She had a somewhat cynical sense of humor and was fiercely loyal to anyone she called friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lana Frederick</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/lana_frederick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/lana_frederick/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Lana Frederick (Maxalis)
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Former Prostitute, turned freelance adventurer
Date of Birth: May 12, 3023
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;7&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 115lbs
Hair Color: Royal Blue with white streak
Eye Color: Golden Yellow
Physical Description: Lana has a toned body of medium height with stark, nearly alabaster skin, golden yellow eyes, and dark, royal blue hair with a white streak running fertically through it. She has a bushy, fox-like tail that is also blue, with a white tip, and her ears are slightly pointed, and bear tufts of blue fur sprouting from those tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/laser/</guid>
      <description>Light Amplification through the Stimulated Emission of Radiation. Lasers have been around for a long, long time, and over the years they have been continually refined, adjusted, and tweaked until they finally became more than simple communications and entertainment tools.
Since the days of the first laser satellite defense systems the technology has advanced with increasing speed. Basically nothing more than a coherent beam of light at a single, controllable, frequency/wavelength, it was always known that they could be used as weapons, but the big question at hand was always, how do we provide enough energy in a small enough package to make them practical and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lintang Kampong</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/lintang_kampong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/lintang_kampong/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Lintang Kampong
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Features/Places of Note Government History Spoilers Status:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loch Moore</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/loch_moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/loch_moore/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Loch Moore
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Loch Moore is a small frontier town on the edge of the Burning Expanse. Its people are mostly simple farmers and live stock handlers, with a few artisans having taken up residence as the town becomes more and more popular among wayward adventurers on their way into the Burning Expanse in search of fortune and glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luna</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/luna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/luna/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Luna
Other Names: The Moon
Location: Earth Orbit
Permanent Population: 4 billion
Transient Population: 1 million to 10 million souls
Imports: Nearly everything. The moon produces little in the way of real consumables or equipment, although it is the entertainment capital of the Sol system, boasting several major film companies and numerous other entertainment companies as well.
Exports: Movies and entertainment mostly.
Description The moon is now by far the most populace world in the Sol system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lycanthrope</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/lycanthrope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/lycanthrope/</guid>
      <description>Lycanthropes are a curiosity in Kalijor. There are two different veins of the race, the canine and the feline. While it is not known how either race originated, what is known is that the different veins propagate differently. The canine lycanthropes pass on their lycanthropy through the exchange of bodily fluids, saliva, blood and the like. They are a particularly aggressive species that is not well liked by any of the other civilized races and due to their inability (or refusal) to accept more civilized ways of living, they have been hunted to near extinction by the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Academy</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/magic_academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/magic_academy/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Magic Academy
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Magic Academy is the paragon of higher learning for mages in Kalijor. The structure itself is something of a curiosity. A two-hundred foot high monolith of solid stone set in a small clearing in the western Forest of Brume, it has one door at it&amp;rsquo;s base and can be walked around in less than a minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malice</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/malice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/malice/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Malice Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Warrior
Date of Birth: Unknown
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;4&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 230lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Brown
Physical Description: Malice is tall, wears coal black armor and wields a huge, claymore-sized black magic sword.
General Description Malice is a bastard, pure and simple. He enjoys causing pain and suffering in others and seems to derive no greater satisfaction than causing someone to break down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mars</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/mars/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Mars
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population: 3.5 Billion
Transient Population:
Imports: People, medical supplies.
Exports: Food, manufactured goods.
Description Mars has been adopted as the agricultural capital of the Sol system. Their hydroponics technology is unrivaled and their food output is nearly twice what is required to feed the entire Sol system. Over the last hundred years or so they have turned their technical expertise to the manufacture of goods as well as food and have rapidly become the center of production as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mars Station</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/mars_station/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/mars_station/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Mars Station
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports: Nearly everything, although they are supported with food and goods from Mars directly.
Exports: None. The station exists merely to act as an intermediary for Martian commerce.
Description The Mars space station is the oldest original station still in operation today. It has been retrofitted and overhauled more times than anyone can remember and continues to be modified to this day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mary</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/mary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/mary/</guid>
      <description>In early 2250, T.R.I.P. enganged in the very first complete human DNA wash on a living, grown person. Before this event, any complete alterations of an individual&amp;rsquo;s DNA were made to zygot before implantation in a parent/host for normal gestation, or to be grown in an artificial womb. The only &amp;lsquo;live&amp;rsquo; DNA alterations made before this breakthrough expirament were extremeley minor and took months, or years, to become outwardly visible. Things such as altering a person&amp;rsquo;s hair, or eye color, or skin pigmentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minotaur</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/minotaur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/minotaur/</guid>
      <description>Minotaur are a bovine species that look like a hybrid of a human and a bull (This is not the case however, and will incur their wrath if it is suggested in their presence). They are covered in coarse hair, have hooves for feet, human-like hands and the head of a large bull. Minotaur are extremely strong and make excellent fighters/warriors. Their race is honorable and proud, but not to a fault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobius Industries</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/mobius_industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/mobius_industries/</guid>
      <description>One of the five corporations that make up The Conglomerate. Mobius Industries is the Sol system’s forerunner in communications, propulsion, and weapon systems for ships. The company opened its doors in the late twenty-second century as a contractor to the US/Chinese government’s space program and quickly evolved into a major power in the world’s corporate landscape as their technology pushed the human race outward from the Earth. No other corporation in human history has made more significant advancements in those fields and Mobius Industries is unique amongst all of the other major corporations of the world in that they have become so influential solely through the continuation of their original product line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monomolecular Blade</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/monomolecular_blade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/monomolecular_blade/</guid>
      <description>The monomolecular sword or knife is an extremely expensive, and dangerous alternative to the standard swords and knives that have been around for centuries.
The basic idea is still the same however. To make a melee weapon that is as sharp as you can possibly make it and will, in the hands of the correct wielder, be an extremely effective weapon. In the case of these weapons there is a wire or filament that is formed from a super dense alloy (although really almost any substance will work as long as it is ferrous).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neo Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/neo-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/neo-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Neo-Tokyo
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Features/Places of Note Government History Spoilers Status:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Niko Nori</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/niko_nori/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/niko_nori/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Niko Nori
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Retired Runner
Date of Birth:
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;7&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 185lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Brown
Physical Description:
General Description Alina Martin&amp;rsquo;s frined, partner, and lover.
Skills of Note Equipment of Note History Spoilers Status: Living</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Wastes</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/northern_wastes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/northern_wastes/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Northern Wastes
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Northern wastes is a region of snowy land nestled in a hollow depression on the west side of Mount Telemon. The hollow is surrounded on all sides by impassible mountains, making the only easy access to the Northern Wastes through the city of Talanor. The region is frigid cold, and under constant cover of blizzard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuiri Qatnio</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/nuiri-qatnio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/nuiri-qatnio/</guid>
      <description>(Noo-e-ree Kat-nee-oh) A Nuiri-Qatnio is the extremely rare occurrence of a child of a Psi-line and a Gene-line character, that inherits the majority of the genetic traits/abilities/features from BOTH of their parents. Most Nuiri-Qatnios die within 1D4 years of being born due to the extreme nature of the forces at work within their bodies. Those that do survive, usually have a difficult life ahead of them. Nuiri-Qatnios are feared by most people for their abilities and appearance, and to make matters worse, they are often afflicted with some form of mental problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obscuri</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/obscuri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/obscuri/</guid>
      <description>Obscuri are a race of elves that have evolved along very different lines from their other brothers and sisters. Long ago, during the ancient wars that threatened to destroy all of Kalijor, a group of elves developed new forms of immensely powerful magic which they used to imbue a number of artifacts with supernatural abilities unheard of previously. These elves then used these items to bring peace to Kalijor. But the peace was short lived as other races began to realize what level of power these elves had achieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ogre</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/ogre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/ogre/</guid>
      <description>Ogres are tall, thickly built creatures that carry enormous physical strength as their primary attribute. They have little or no hair on their bodies, both male and female, and any hair they do have tends to be wispy and light in color, to the point of being nearly undetectable under casual scrutiny. They appear as huge, lumbering brutes and indeed are among the strongest sentient races of Kalijor. Most ogres are of average intelligence but some have proven themselves to be extremely intelligent, to the point of becoming extremely adept mages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onoba</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/onoba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/onoba/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Onoba
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Onoba is the name given to the home of the Obscuri. While the Obscuri themselves are beyond such things as names, no attempt has been made to discourage the use of this name and so it has become the common name of their place of residence. Onoba is a city that has been molded into the interior of the peaks of the Uraval Mountains .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orc</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/orc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/orc/</guid>
      <description>Orcs are tribal creatures that typically shun more civilized life and live in small to medium sized groups in the wilds of Kalijor. Their physical size and appearance varies wildly based upon what region they hail from and orcs are unique among most other species of Kalijor in that they very quickly develop physical adaptations to better help them survive in their environment. As an example, it has been noted that orcs that are forced to vacate their lands for new environments will develop new skin coloration and markings and even dramatically change size to better acclimatize themselves to their new environs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandoria</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/pandoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/pandoria/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Pandoria
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Pandoria is a city that was created in a pocket dimension. The only way to get to Pandoria is by one of the two portals that connect it to Kalijor. One is in the great portal chamber in Rathalon and the other is a larger portal that is deep within the forest of Brume . The city itself is grown into a forest of massive hardwood trees that are magically grown and shaped by Druids to suit the needs of the city and its inhabitants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Particle Beam</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/particle_beam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/particle_beam/</guid>
      <description>Particle beams are weapons that accelerate atomic or sub-atomic particles to within a few percent of the speed of light and then direct them at a target through a series of electrostatic (not electromagnetic) focusing/acceleration arrays. Essentially they are very similar to rail guns or electromagnetic mass drivers except that they use electrostatic forces rather than electromagnetic, and they are firing beams of particles rather than solid slugs or projectiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pincher</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/pincher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/pincher/</guid>
      <description>Pinchers are the future equivilent of cat burglers. These individuals are skilled in many areas of subterfuge, hacking, breaking and entering, and other, similar activities. Pinchers are master thieves, able to break through the toughest of physical security systems and most computer security as well. While their computer skills do not extend into the same realms as Digerati they are still quite adept. While a good Digerati can break through sophisticated security and hop across networks and systems with the greatest of ease, the average Pincher will instead dance through the physical security measures to get inside where the computer security is nowhere near as strong as it is outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Of Serenity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_serenity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_serenity/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Plain of Serenity
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Plane of Serenity is a huge expanse of grasslands that lay to the west of Rathalon and north of the Forest of Brume. These grasslands play host to most of the agriculture that feeds the many citizens of Rathalon. There are a few goblins that make their home on the western edge of the plane in a small tangled forest that surrounds a dilapidated old stone tower, but otherwise the area is free of most predators and well patrolled by the Rathalon guard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Of Sorrow</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_sorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_sorrow/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Plain of Sorrow
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Plane of Sorrow is the name given to the area east of the Uraval Mountains. The entire area is collectively known as the dark side of Kalijor but the Plane of Sorrow is its actual name. This region is enormous, and featureless. It is covered in a thick, reddish-orange silt-like material that is just moist enough to stick to everything, but doesn&amp;rsquo;t carry enough moisture to actually prove useful for anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psi Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/psi-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/psi-line/</guid>
      <description>Psi-Line Humans are those that have undergone extensive modification through genetic engineering or are the children of thusly-engineered individuals. The end result of the genetic engineering is that the Psi-line humans have developed psionic powers to some extent. The range of their powers varies greatly from one individual to the next, but none of them has anything less than minor psionic aptitude.
The genetic modifications these individuals or their parents have undergone have almost all centered around the mind and other neurological systems of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>På Rymi</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/p%C3%A5-rymi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/p%C3%A5-rymi/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: På-rymi
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Features/Places of Note Government History Spoilers Status:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quark Industries</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/quark_industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/quark_industries/</guid>
      <description>One of the five corporations that make up The Conglomerate. Quark Industries began life as a weapon systems research and development firm for one of the major world governments in the late twenty-first century. In the centuries since then they have branched out into every conceivable industry and area of research. Of the five major companies that are members of the Conglomerate, Quark Industries is by far the most well-liked by the general population.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rathalon</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/rathalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/rathalon/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Rathalon
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The unofficial capital city of Kalijor , Rathalon is by far the largest city in the world. It was carved by the best dwarven craftsmen in the world along with assistance from some of the cleverest mages since the great wars. Not a single piece of stone was added to the city during its construction. Even the doors are carved from the stone where they stand, and are operated through magical enchantments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renchi Kas</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/renchi-kas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/renchi-kas/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Renchi-kas
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Features/Places of Note Government History Spoilers Status:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reptilian</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/reptilian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/reptilian/</guid>
      <description>Reptilians are a race of highly evolved reptiles, just as their name would suggest. Reptilians are usually thin, but strong, and light in weight. They usually have no body hair what so ever, although the occasional reptilian has been seen with a mane of thick, straight hairs on their neck. What causes this is unknown and it is extremely rare. Their skin is covered in scales that range from medium to coarse in texture and a variety of patterns and ridges can be seen from family line to family line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resonance</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/resonance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/resonance/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Resonance (Real name unknown)
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Singer/Entertainer
Date of Birth: Unknown
Height: Exact Height Unknown, looks to be just under six feet.
Weight: Unknown, looks to weigh around 130lbs
Hair Color: Metallic Platinum
Eye Color: Golden yellow
Physical Description: Resonance looks elvish, with a slight build and elegant features. She has long, tapered ears that end in delicate points and she appears to use them to express emotions much like the elves in Kalijor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhaeton</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/rhaeton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/rhaeton/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Rhaeton
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Thief/Rogue
Date of Birth: 35 years old
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;9&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 125lbs
Hair Color: Fiery Red
Eye Color: Cobalt
Physical Description: Rhaeton was of average height for a half-elf, with dark blue eyes and flaming red hair.
General Description Rhaeton was abandoned by her parents in the city of Pandoria at a young age, leaving her to fend for herself. She was jaded at an an early age due to circumstances but still tried to keep a sense of humor about her, even if it was a bit dry and had a mean streak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riana Shandra Thorindal</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/riana_shandra_thorindal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/riana_shandra_thorindal/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Riana Shandra Thorindal Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Spell-Sword in Kalijor, Corporate Courier in the real world
Date of Birth: July 14, 3039 in the real world
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo; in both Kalijor and the real world
Weight: 135lbs in Kalijor, 350 lbs in the real world (but looks 135 lbs)
Hair Color: Royal Purple
Eye Color: Violet
Physical Description: Physically, Riana stands around six feet tall and weighs in around one-hundred-thirty pounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riana&#39;S Body</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/rianas_body/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/rianas_body/</guid>
      <description>Riana’s cybernetic body is arguably a product of the most advanced and forward thinking technology known to mankind. It is designed to almost perfectly mimic a normal human body in nearly every way as far as construction and structure are concerned, but enhances, strengthens, and builds upon that construction and form immeasurably. Her skeleton is composed of a carbon-carbon honeycomb that is laced/reinforced and sheathed in 6.6.2 Titanium. This makes her bones both extremely light, and incredibly resilient to breaking, shattering and other forms of damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samantha Cobb</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/samantha_cobb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/samantha_cobb/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Samantha Georgia Cobb
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Medical Doctor and Doctor of Cybernetics
Date of Birth: February 18, 3008
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;8&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 135lbs
Hair Color: Dark Aubern
Eye Color: Hazel Green
Physical Description: Sam is a woman of medium height and build with dark hair and hazel eyes. She tends to dress simply but smartly and does her best not to draw attention to the fact that she is considerably wealthy, both by inheritance and from her practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturn</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/saturn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/saturn/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Saturn
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population: Ten to 15 million souls.
Transient Population: 10,000 to 20,000 souls
Imports: People, Machinery, Medical supplies, Food.
Exports: Raw materials in the form of gasses and minerals mined from the planet itself and its thirty some moons.
Description The Saturn community is very similar to Jupiter in that it consists of numerous basses and stations that reside on the surface of many of the planet’s moons, and in orbit around the planet itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalarythica</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/scalarythica/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/scalarythica/</guid>
      <description>These animals resemble a short, fat alligator with twelve short, fat tentacles instead of normal legs. They have a jaw full of short, pointy teeth and are voracious predators. They hunt and travel in packs, using coordinated efforts and tactics, often driving prey into ambushes and using terrain features to their advantage. They are incredibly fast considering their bulk, especially in tight spaces and obstructed environments such as forests and jungles where their many flexible appendages offer them excellent footing and balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sean</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/sean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/sean/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: SEAN
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation:
Date of Birth:
Height: N/A
Weight: N/A
Hair Color: N/A
Eye Color: N/A
Physical Description:
General Description An Artificial Intelligence designed specifically for use by Emil Frederick in his personal shuttle, The Kitsune. SEAN is responsible for the operation of the ship as well as being Doctor Frederick&amp;rsquo;s personal companion during his self-imposed exile from all things corporate. SEAN is an extremely intelligent, insightful, and fully functioning intelligence with real emotions and an understanding of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selendria</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/selendria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/selendria/</guid>
      <description>Selendria is the name of Jumah&amp;rsquo;s magical weapon. It was forged by an ancient elven smith and has been passed down through his family for centuries. The weapon is a small shaft of about 4 feet in length that is capped on either end by a straight, narrow blade, each about 2 feet in length. The weapon is a powerful magical item that allows its wielder to parry or block magical bolts and other similar attacks, harmlessly dissipating them into the air around the weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solidarity Online</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/solidarity_online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/solidarity_online/</guid>
      <description>The company responsible for the creation, maintenance and operation of the Kalijor fantasy MMO. Despite Kalijor&amp;rsquo;s significance in the corporate setting, Solidarity Online is ~not~ a member of The Conglomerate. Although it remains uncertain if this fact is due to the Conglomerate&amp;rsquo;s decision, or if it is Solidarity Onine&amp;rsquo;s desire to remain unaffiliated. Solidarity Online operates dozens of different MMO&amp;rsquo;s all of which are very successful and cover a myriad of genre, but Kalijor is by far their most well known and successful game world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southern Plain Of Serenity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_plain_of_serenity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_plain_of_serenity/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Southern Plain of Serenity
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Southern Plane of Serenity rests between the southern edge of the Forest of Brume and the Northern edge of the Burning Expanse. On its western edge is the great sea and to the East is the Uraval Mountain&amp;rsquo;s southern tip and the great stone tree that is home to the city of Avian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southern Wastes</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_wastes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_wastes/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Southern Wastes
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The southern Wastes is a cold, snowy expanse that rests between the Northern gate of Rathalon and the southern entrance to Talanor. The area is almost always covered in snow, although it does clear up a bit in the summer months. Snow storms are frequent but not constant and the region has several well maintained roads leading from Talanor to Rathalon and the surrounding areas, although if a traveler leaves the safety of the patrolled roads they are likely to run into some of the orcs that live in the numerous ruins and fallen structures of the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft Technology</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/spacecraft_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/spacecraft_technology/</guid>
      <description>Space craft are now fairly commonplace with models available for prices that the upper middle class can begin to afford. Space travel is still not tightly regulated in open space, although flying in or near an inhabited body (Meaning planet, moon, asteroid, space station, etc) requires a pilot’s license and all of the appropriate clearances from ground control for the air-space in question.
There are a myriad of different types and designs of space craft available, ranging from sleek, sexy two-seaters to family size six to ten passenger ships, then up into cargo hauling and mobile home sized vessels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T.R.I.P.</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/t.r.i.p./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/t.r.i.p./</guid>
      <description>One of the five corporations that make up The Conglomerate. T.R.I.P. (Technological Radiological Industrial Pharmacological)began life as pharmaceuticals company. They produced most of the major medicines and vaccinations throughout the past five hundred years. As time moved forward, they began designing new machines and methodologies for the evaluation and production of drugs and licensing these new technologies/processes to other companies. As they began to see those new markets open up they continued to branch out into new fields, eventually encompassing nearly every aspect of the average person’s day within their sphere of influence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talanor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/talanor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/talanor/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Talanor
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Talanor is the home of Kalijor&amp;rsquo;s Dwarves and Gnomes. It is a city that is carved out of the belly of Mount Telemon to the north of Rathalon, between the snowy Northern and Southern Wastes. The city maintains a constant level of lighting and temperature day and night, year round which makes it uncomfortable for most surface-dwelling people to handle on a continuous basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanor Na&#39;Ellis</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/tanor_naellis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/tanor_naellis/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Tanor Na&amp;rsquo;Ellis
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Druid
Date of Birth: 250 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;3&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 185lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Green
Physical Description: Tanor is a tall, slightly overweight (for an Elf) Druid that makes his home in Pandoria.
General Description He seems to have high political goals and is of an undetermined level of power as a magic user as no one can seem to remember a time when they have seen him use his abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Line</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tech-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tech-line/</guid>
      <description>Tech-Line Humans are those who have undergone extensive bionic or cybernetic augmentation, to the extent that some have less than 5% of their original body mass still intact. Not all Tech-lines are completely mechanical however, although the majority are over 50% artificial. Many choose to use the more clandestine bio-system augmentations that keep them looking mostly human except for the odd piece here and there, such as a sensor antenna or mechanical eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Astraeus Accord</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_astraeus_accord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_astraeus_accord/</guid>
      <description>Technical Information Full Name: The Astraeus Accord
Aliases: The Accord, The Pact, The Astraeus Act, and &amp;lsquo;dammit, that.&amp;rsquo;
Date Established: December 21, 2721
Affected Parties: All Conglomerate Citizens, all citizens of &amp;lsquo;the Dregs&amp;rsquo;
General Description The Astraeus Accord outlines the relationship between The Conglomerate and the dregs. The accord details political roles and responsabilities of both parties as well as social and economical concerns and relationships.
Under the Astraeus Accord, it is unlawful for any member of either party to engage in open fighting in any public location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Battle of Titan</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_battle_of_titan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_battle_of_titan/</guid>
      <description>After The Purge it took years for those who lost their homes and families to find a place to put down roots and start building new lives. It was a long time in teh making, but eventually these people etablished a true community based in the asteroid belt.
Being outcasts meant they could be harrassed without consequence or recourse by Conglomerate troops and personnel, so these outcasts, known as dissidents, did everythign they could to keep themselves from being found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blitz</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_blitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_blitz/</guid>
      <description>Early in the year 2800, a series of gang wars broke out in Neo-Tokyo shortly after the Conglomerate withdrew from the city to consolidate power and provide an environment in which they could encourage the growth of a healthy black market. These rival gangs and factions all fought for control of the city and its underworld community. They fought in the alleys and on teh rooftops until their fighting spilled over onto the streets and required the Conglomerate to step in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Conglomerate</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/the_conglomerate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/corporations/the_conglomerate/</guid>
      <description>A corporate government is an interesting prospect at best. The government of the future is formed by an elaborate interweaving of the top-level management from various corporations with extreme, and far-reaching influence. In short, the more powerful a particular corporation is, the more influential they are in the political landscape of humanity.
Just as any corporation&amp;rsquo;s leadership is made up of multiple levels or layers of people, each holding more power or sway than those immediately below them, the Sol system&amp;rsquo;s government is made up of the CEO&amp;rsquo;s of multiple corporations, the more powerful the corporation is, the higher up the chain of command the individual is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_end/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_end/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: The End
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Tor Rayean
Captain: Tor Rayean
Registration Number:
Manufacturer: Mobius Industries
Construction Shipyard: Neo-Tokyo Shipyards (no longer in service)
Launch Date: Januray 18, 2214
Make: Medium Cargo Vessel
Model: MI-88
Centerline: 118 feet
Beam: 118 feet
Dry Weight: 321,000 pounds
Passenger Capacity: 5
Cargo Capacity: 10,000 pounds
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: Single High-Output Ion Drive
Super-Luminal Drive Type: None
Sub-Luminal Cruising Velocity: 30,000 MPH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_future/</guid>
      <description>A brief History of Humanity&amp;rsquo;s Rise Sometime in the late twenty first century, circa 2090, the human race took its first tentative steps off of their home world and began living in space. Their first off-world colonies were in space stations that hung in orbit around the Earth and her moon, Luna. Over the next three-hundred years they continued to branch out and expand across the solar system. New developments in propulsion technology made intra-system travel more like daily commutes, allowing people to travel between the Earth and Luna in a few of hours, and out to more distant planets in a matter of days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kestrel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_kestrel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_kestrel/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: Kestrel
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Solidarity Online
Captain: Willhelmina and Riana
Registration Number:
Manufacturer: Quark Industries
Construction Shipyard: Utopia Planitia
Launch Date: September 1st, 3039
Make: Medium Shuttle
Model: QI-PS111
Centerline: 78 feet
Beam: 22 feet (fusilage), 63 feet (wing-tip to wing-tip)
Dry Weight: 24,000 pounds
Passenger Capacity: 2
Cargo Capacity: 1,500 pounds
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: Twin Ion
Super-Luminal Drive Type: Traction
Sub-Luminal Cruising Velocity: 57,000 MPH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kitsune</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_kitsune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_kitsune/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: Kitsune
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Doctor Emil Frederick
Captain: Lana Frederick
Registration Number:
Manufacturer: Mobius Industries
Construction Shipyard: Titan Shipyard
Launch Date:
Make: Large Shuttle
Model: MI-LS18-C
Centerline: 121 feet
Beam: 34 feet (fusilage), 91 feet (wing-tip to wing-tip)
Dry Weight: 38,000 pounds
Passenger Capacity: 6
Cargo Capacity: 3,000 pounds
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: Twin High-Output Plasma
Super-Luminal Drive Type: None
Sub-Luminal Cruising Velocity: 50,000 MPH
Sub-Luminal Maximum Velocity: 58,000 MPH</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Methuselah</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_methuselah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_methuselah/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: Methuselah
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Aegis Online
Captain: Sean Flannery
Registration Number:
Manufacturer: Mobius Industries
Construction Shipyard: Venus Station
Launch Date: August 1, 3040
Make: Heavy Cruiser
Model: MI-XC05-CHC
Centerline: 1,258 feet
Beam: 348 feet
Dry Weight: 105,000 tons
Passenger Capacity: 35 officers, 1,750 enlisted, and up to 200 passengers
Cargo Capacity: Up to 500 tons, not counting auxiliary craft and ordinance/supplies
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: 16 High-Output Heavy Plasma</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Neophyte&#39;S Serendipity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_neophytes_serendipity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_neophytes_serendipity/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: Neophyte&amp;rsquo;s Serendipity
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Vincent Torres
Captain: Vincent Torres
Registration Number: NX-1138
Manufacturer: Cold Fusion
Construction Shipyard:
Launch Date: June 27, 2778
Make: Medium Cargo, converted from Large Scout
Model: CF1811-B, &amp;lsquo;Yampa&amp;rsquo; class light freighter
Centerline: 131 feet
Beam: 48 feet (fusilage), 110 feet (wing-tip to wing-tip)
Dry Weight: 310,000 pounds
Passenger Capacity: 5
Cargo Capacity: 44,000 pounds
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: Two High-Output Heavy Ion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purge</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/misc/the_purge/</guid>
      <description>As cybernetic and genetic technology advanced, the human race began a slow but stead divergence into multiple &amp;lsquo;post-human&amp;rsquo; groups. The pace of the technology and alterations steadily increased over the years, creating larger and larger numbers of psychics or Psi-Lines, genetically altered or Gene-Lines, and technologically altered or Tech-Line individuals. These changes, combined with a slow but general acceptance of &amp;lsquo;post-human&amp;rsquo; individuals continued widening the gulf between groups, but never truly allowed them to diverge into separate species.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Riotous Good Time</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_riotous_good_time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_riotous_good_time/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: Riotous Good Time
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Kaden McGinley
Captain: Kaden McGinley
Registration Number:
Manufacturer: Cold Fusion
Construction Shipyard: Earth Ring Station
Launch Date: April 18, 2852
Make: Medium Passenger converted to hybrid Passenger/Cargo
Model: CF223-C1
Centerline: 79 feet
Beam: 21 feet (fusilage), 66 feet (wing-tip to wing-tip)
Dry Weight: 28,000 pounds
Passenger Capacity: 6
Cargo Capacity: 5,000 pounds
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: Two High-Output Ion
Super-Luminal Drive Type: None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seraphim</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_seraphim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/vehicles/the_seraphim/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Registered Name: Seraphim
Aliases:
Registered Owner: Niko Nori
Captain: Niko Nori, although it is more often piloted by Alina Martin
Registration Number:
Manufacturer: Unknown
Construction Shipyard: Ceres
Launch Date: Unknown
Make: Small Shuttle
Model: Unknown
Centerline: 36 feet
Beam: 11 feet (fusilage), 28 feet (wing-tip to wing-tip)
Dry Weight: 13,000 pounds
Passenger Capacity: 2
Cargo Capacity: Minimal, around 250 pounds
Sub-Luminal Drive Type: Two High-Output Plasma
Super-Luminal Drive Type: None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tyconderoga</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/the_tyconderoga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/the_tyconderoga/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: The Tyconderoga
Other Names:
Location: Earth-Luna L1 LaGrange point
Permanent Population: 8,000 souls plus or minus about 10%.
Transient Population: Maybe as many as a hundred, usually much less.
Imports: Everything
Exports: Nothing
Description The Tyconderoga is a large space station built and occupied by Solidarity Online. The station is positioned in the L1 Lagrange Point between Earth and Luna, and has been the sole facility of the corporation since it was brought online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tor Rayean</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tor_rayean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/tor_rayean/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Tor Rayean
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Runner
Date of Birth:
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;
Weight: 185lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Brown
Physical Description: Tor is of medium height and build, with dark eyes and generally greasy hair. He does little in the way of making himself pallatable to anyone and is the sort of person that most other folks instinctively give a wide berth.
General Description Tor is a scumbag, pure and simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tranquility</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/tranquility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/tranquility/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Tranquility
Other Names:
Location: Luna, The sea of Tranquility
Permanent Population: Five-hundred Million
Transient Population: Twenty Million to fifty million souls.
Imports: Nearly everything but very basic food and goods that can be produced locally.
Exports: None per se. Luna in general and Tranquility in particular are teh entertainment capitol of teh Sol system, so a great many celebrities and movie studios reside here.
Description The domed city of Tranquility is the largest city/structure on the surface of the moon, being more than five-hundred square miles in size and playing host to around five-hundred million permanent residents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troll</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/troll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/troll/</guid>
      <description>Trolls are tall, skinny, physically powerful, and normally assumed to be not terribly bright, although this often proves to be a fatal mistake to make. They range in color from yellow, through green, brown, and reddish colors. Trolls normally have large tufts of hair sticking out all over their bodies in strange directions with no apparent rhyme or reason to their placement. Their facial features are gaunt, angular, and almost all severely pointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turin Glastnost</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/turin_glastnost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/turin_glastnost/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Turin Glastnost
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Psychic/Criminal Mastermind
Date of Birth: January 1, 2999
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 190lbs
Hair Color: Dark Brown
Eye Color: Dark Hazel
Physical Description: Turin is an amazing physical specimine, with dark hair, dark eyes, a fit body, and a poise and confidence born from a lifetime of successes. Turin is a snappy dresser and has only the best things money can buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uraval Mountains</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/uraval_mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/uraval_mountains/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Uraval Mountains
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description The Uraval Mountains are a range of extremely high, sheer-walled peaks that runs from the City of Rathalon (which is carved from the head of the mountain range), southward to Avian, dividing Kalijor cleanly in half and separating the light side and the dark side with an impassable wall of solid stone.
The range is several miles wide and a thousand miles long and anyone who has ever attempted to climb it in any way, has either turned back before they get anywhere near the summit, fallen to their death, or disappeared and is never seen again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vargrus Valkyrie</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/vargrus_valkyrie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/vargrus_valkyrie/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Vargrus Valkyrie
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Martial Artist
Date of Birth: 98 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;
Weight: 200lbs
Hair Color: None
Eye Color: Brown
Physical Description:
General Description Calm, cool and collected. Vargrus was the pillar that held up the group when all else was falling down around them. Likewise he was also the infuriatingly calm and imperturbable one of the group. He was a fiercely loyal man who always held to his convictions no matter the pressures around him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venus</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/venus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/venus/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Venus
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population: Varies, normally around 200 million.
Transient Population:
Imports: Food, water, labor, machine parts
Exports: Heavy metals, minerals, silicates and other raw materials used in the construction of computers, weapons, equipment, and ships.
Description Venus is a violent and dangerous place for even the most well-prepared individuals. Its atmosphere is acidic and ranges from hundreds of degrees to thousands of degrees in temperature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venus Station</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/venus_station/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/venus_station/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Venus Station
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population: Around four billion souls
Transient Population:
Imports: Food, Raw materials both organic and non-organic, prefabricated starship components.
Exports: Starships (both sub-luminal and super-luminal).
Description While the Earth Ring Station is the largest man-made structure in teh Sol System, The Venus Station is by far the oldest, and densest. What started off as a simple way-station in orbit around Venus has, over the past 5 centuries, transformed into a small, artificial moon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincent Torres</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/vincent_torres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/vincent_torres/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Vincent (Vin) Mathew Torres Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Pilot/Runner, runs a small charter/cargo business out of Earth Station
Date of Birth: October 3, 3012
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;4&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 210lbs
Hair Color: Blond
Eye Color: Blue
Physical Description:
General Description Vincent is tall, athletic, and charismatic. He loves the small pleasures in life and does not play by other people&amp;rsquo;s rules. He has fallen deeply in love with Riana after only one meeting and looks forward to any time at all that they can spend together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wayne Nelson</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/wayne_nelson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/wayne_nelson/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Wayne Edward Nelson
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Cybernetic Engineer
Date of Birth: July 21, 2998
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;2&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 110lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Hazel Green
Physical Description: Wayne is an extremely short man with a balled crown surrounded by wispy dark hair and a goblin-like face with a long pointed nose and protruding eyebrow ridges. He is generally unpleasant and doesn’t care at all what anyone else thinks about him as long as they know he is smarter than them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weapon Classifications</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/weapon_classifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-future/weapon_classifications/</guid>
      <description>Weapons are broken down into classes based upon several factors. Range, Ammunition type (where applicable), damage potential versus organic materials (people), Damage potential versus inorganic materials (structures and vehicles), Weight, and Legality.
Class A Class A weapons are weapons with limited or no range, blunt or sharp edges designed to cause damage through various forms of bashing, smashing, slicing, chopping, piercing, etc. Examples of Class A weapons would include Swords, Staves, Axes, Knives, Maces, Clubs, Cudgels, Spears, Pole-arms and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weapon Technology</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/weapon_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/technology/weapon_technology/</guid>
      <description>With all of the advances in technology that seem to permeate the everyday lives of the citizens of the Sol System it is often asked, why are there not more advanced weapons in use? The answers are myriad and varied depending upon whom you are speaking to, however there are a few that are commonly cited, and ring true. To begin with, are there more advanced personal weapons available? Absolutely. Examples of which follow this article for those that are curious for more information but include briefly, coherent light energy weapons or lasers, charged particle weapons, or particle beams, ionizing gas discharge or plasma weapons, and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Willhelmina Orlova</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/willhelmina_orlova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/willhelmina_orlova/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Willhelmina Katarina Orlova Aliases:
Avatar/Player: Katrina Annwyn Thorindal
Occupation: Courier for Solidarity Online
Date of Birth: April 28, 3011
Height: 5&amp;rsquo;11&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 130lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Emerald Green
Physical Description:
General Description Willhelmina is a twenty-four year old woman who has spent more than half of her life almost continuously connected to Kalijor, in order to keep the character of Katrina as real as possible to Riana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wyndel</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/wyndel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/wyndel/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Wyndel
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: Mage
Date of Birth: 4788 years old
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 135lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Grey
Physical Description:
General Description Aloof and contemplative, Wyndel seemed a great and powerful elf until his evil streak revealed itself when his wife Annwyn was revealed to be pregnant. Wyndel turned out to be evil to the core. He was cold, calculating, and methodical in his planning and execution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xaman Otoch</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/xaman-otoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-future/xaman-otoch/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Name: Xaman-Otoch
Other Names:
Location:
Permanent Population:
Transient Population:
Imports:
Exports:
Description Features/Places of Note Government History Spoilers Status:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xanthe</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/xanthe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-kalijor/xanthe/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Xanthe
Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: N/A
Date of Birth: 1 year old
Height: 4&amp;rsquo; (15&amp;rsquo; in length)
Weight: 900lbs
Hair Color: None (His scales are pearlescent/mother of pearl)
Eye Color: Blue
Physical Description: He is around fifteen feet long and four feet high at the shoulder. His neck is around four feet long and his body around three and a half feet. The rest of him is all thickly muscled and nearly prehensile tail that ends in a knot of bone that is shaped like a sharply pointed chisel or gladius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Quinn</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/xavier_quinn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/people-future/xavier_quinn/</guid>
      <description>Vital Statistics Full Name: Xavier David Quinn Aliases:
Avatar/Player:
Occupation: CEO, Solidarity Online
Date of Birth: 2992
Height: 6&amp;rsquo;1&amp;rdquo;
Weight: 211lbs
Hair Color: Black
Eye Color: Grey
Physical Description: He stands just over six feet tall and has dark hair that falls to the middle of his back and is always restrained in a pony tail and very well maintained, never a single strand out of place. He wears a well trimmed Mustache that falls down on either side of his mouth, merging seamlessly into his equally well trimmed beard leaving his jaw and face free of hair except around the chin and under the nose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xeracra</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/xeracra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/xeracra/</guid>
      <description>Xeracra are large cat-like creatures with thinly placed, thick-bristled hair that is a sickly grey color. They have six powerful, stocky limbs that make them both swift and silent. Their mouth is like a great shark’s with multiple rows of short, serrated teeth that all point back toward the animal’s throat. They have four eyes, two vivid green orbs set into the front of their head, and two glossy black ones that are much smaller and positioned one on either side of the animal’s head, just in front of its huge ears that each sport a tuft of hairs sprouting from its extreme tip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zyrik</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/zyrik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/weapons-kalijor/zyrik/</guid>
      <description>Zyrik the Dragon Slayer was forged by the dwarven masters in the mystical forges of Kalek&amp;rsquo;Tinal untold ages ago. The weapon was created with the singular purpose of laying waste to the scourge of dragons that had befallen Kalijor and crushed the will of its people beneath their scaly might. The weapon is imbued with the power to do incredible amounts of damage to beings with draconic blood coursing through their veins but its most devastating power was not even conceived of by the greatest craftsmen and mages on Kalijor until the day it was invoked by its wielder.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>