<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creatures of Kalijor on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creatures of Kalijor on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dwarf</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/dwarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/dwarf/</guid>
      <description>Dwarves are a subterranean race that are intelligent, belligerent, and extremely capable builders and excavators. As a rule, dwarves make excellent craftsmen and artisans, some of the finest weapons and armor in Kalijor have been credited back to dwarven craftsmen. Dwarves and elves tend not to get along very well due to some ancient hostility between their two peoples, although not openly combative under normal circumstances, it takes very little coaxing to get a dwarf to into a confrontation with an elf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elf</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/elf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/elf/</guid>
      <description>Elves are an elegant, intelligent, and prideful people. They are the masters of whatever they undertake, always striving to be without peer. It is this attitude which is said to have led to the great war millennia ago when elven and dwarven craftsmen were driven to war over the subject of who’s skills where the better when it came to forging magical weapons. Since that war the elves have almost entirely given up the art of metal working, preferring instead to devote themselves to nature, magic and wood working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equun Draco</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/equun-draco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/equun-draco/</guid>
      <description>This creature is a strange cross between a dragon and a horse. Their legs are strong and thick with muscles with clawed toes in any number from two to five. They have long necks, usually about the same length as their body, that are very flexible and fully articulate. They have long, whip-like tails that are anywhere from two to three times the length of their bodies and end in some form of bone blade, or club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Felinoid</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/felinoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/felinoid/</guid>
      <description>Felinoids appear to be a combination of cats and humans. They are covered in fur, which is typically short and soft although some have had coarse or long fur, from head to toe. They have pointed, articulated ears, whiskers, slitted pupils, a keen sense of smell and retractable claws in their fingers and toes. Most felinoids have tails and their coloring and patterning ranges all over the place, some following similar designs as typical big game cats, others more like the more domesticated house cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gnome</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/gnome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/gnome/</guid>
      <description>Gnomes are small, generally frail looking individuals that normally live in subterranean locations. They are smaller even than dwarves but seem to share their same brash attitudes, tending to think everyone else is intellectually inferior to them despite any illustrations to the contrary. Gnomes are consummate tinkerers, always trying to invent or improve things in strange new ways. The studious nature of gnomes makes them excellent mages while their small stature makes them a poor choice for physical combat, although such things are not entirely unheard of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goblin</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/goblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/goblin/</guid>
      <description>Goblins are short, hairless humanoids that are particularly clever in the ways of misdirection. They Have long, pointy ears, inky black eyes, and four digits on each hand/foot. Their size ranges from around two feet to nearly four feet and their color is usually some shade of green, although some yellows and greys are not unheard of. Goblins enjoy games of trickery and chance and make excellent thieves.
Average Life Span: 100 to 250 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/human/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/human/</guid>
      <description>Humans are by far the most plentiful race in Kalijor. They range in skin tones from pale white through dark brown, almost ebony. They are an intelligent race that learns quickly but oft times makes rash decisions as they are still quite young, in racial terms. Their life span is short in comparison to the other major races of Kalijor with most living around eighty years although some have lived well into their hundreds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lycanthrope</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/lycanthrope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/lycanthrope/</guid>
      <description>Lycanthropes are a curiosity in Kalijor. There are two different veins of the race, the canine and the feline. While it is not known how either race originated, what is known is that the different veins propagate differently. The canine lycanthropes pass on their lycanthropy through the exchange of bodily fluids, saliva, blood and the like. They are a particularly aggressive species that is not well liked by any of the other civilized races and due to their inability (or refusal) to accept more civilized ways of living, they have been hunted to near extinction by the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minotaur</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/minotaur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/minotaur/</guid>
      <description>Minotaur are a bovine species that look like a hybrid of a human and a bull (This is not the case however, and will incur their wrath if it is suggested in their presence). They are covered in coarse hair, have hooves for feet, human-like hands and the head of a large bull. Minotaur are extremely strong and make excellent fighters/warriors. Their race is honorable and proud, but not to a fault.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obscuri</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/obscuri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/obscuri/</guid>
      <description>Obscuri are a race of elves that have evolved along very different lines from their other brothers and sisters. Long ago, during the ancient wars that threatened to destroy all of Kalijor, a group of elves developed new forms of immensely powerful magic which they used to imbue a number of artifacts with supernatural abilities unheard of previously. These elves then used these items to bring peace to Kalijor. But the peace was short lived as other races began to realize what level of power these elves had achieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ogre</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/ogre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/ogre/</guid>
      <description>Ogres are tall, thickly built creatures that carry enormous physical strength as their primary attribute. They have little or no hair on their bodies, both male and female, and any hair they do have tends to be wispy and light in color, to the point of being nearly undetectable under casual scrutiny. They appear as huge, lumbering brutes and indeed are among the strongest sentient races of Kalijor. Most ogres are of average intelligence but some have proven themselves to be extremely intelligent, to the point of becoming extremely adept mages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orc</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/orc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/orc/</guid>
      <description>Orcs are tribal creatures that typically shun more civilized life and live in small to medium sized groups in the wilds of Kalijor. Their physical size and appearance varies wildly based upon what region they hail from and orcs are unique among most other species of Kalijor in that they very quickly develop physical adaptations to better help them survive in their environment. As an example, it has been noted that orcs that are forced to vacate their lands for new environments will develop new skin coloration and markings and even dramatically change size to better acclimatize themselves to their new environs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reptilian</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/reptilian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/reptilian/</guid>
      <description>Reptilians are a race of highly evolved reptiles, just as their name would suggest. Reptilians are usually thin, but strong, and light in weight. They usually have no body hair what so ever, although the occasional reptilian has been seen with a mane of thick, straight hairs on their neck. What causes this is unknown and it is extremely rare. Their skin is covered in scales that range from medium to coarse in texture and a variety of patterns and ridges can be seen from family line to family line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalarythica</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/scalarythica/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/scalarythica/</guid>
      <description>These animals resemble a short, fat alligator with twelve short, fat tentacles instead of normal legs. They have a jaw full of short, pointy teeth and are voracious predators. They hunt and travel in packs, using coordinated efforts and tactics, often driving prey into ambushes and using terrain features to their advantage. They are incredibly fast considering their bulk, especially in tight spaces and obstructed environments such as forests and jungles where their many flexible appendages offer them excellent footing and balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troll</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/troll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/troll/</guid>
      <description>Trolls are tall, skinny, physically powerful, and normally assumed to be not terribly bright, although this often proves to be a fatal mistake to make. They range in color from yellow, through green, brown, and reddish colors. Trolls normally have large tufts of hair sticking out all over their bodies in strange directions with no apparent rhyme or reason to their placement. Their facial features are gaunt, angular, and almost all severely pointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xeracra</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/xeracra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/creatures-kalijor/xeracra/</guid>
      <description>Xeracra are large cat-like creatures with thinly placed, thick-bristled hair that is a sickly grey color. They have six powerful, stocky limbs that make them both swift and silent. Their mouth is like a great shark’s with multiple rows of short, serrated teeth that all point back toward the animal’s throat. They have four eyes, two vivid green orbs set into the front of their head, and two glossy black ones that are much smaller and positioned one on either side of the animal’s head, just in front of its huge ears that each sport a tuft of hairs sprouting from its extreme tip.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>