<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Places of Kalijor on Kalijor.com</title>
    <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Places of Kalijor on Kalijor.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avian</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/avian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/avian/</guid>
      <description>title: Avian desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Avian percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Avian Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description Avian is the home of the bird races of Kalijor. The city is nestled into three tiers that are composed of the tightly intertwined branches of a miles high petrified tree on the southern apex of the Uraval Mountains . The tiers of the city each represent a class of people, with the lowest tier being home to the lower class laborers, shops, artisans and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning Expanse</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/burning_expanse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/burning_expanse/</guid>
      <description>title: Burning Expanse desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Burning_Expanse percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: The Burning Expanse Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Burning Expanse is a vast, flat, wasteland of scorching sand and heat. There is no water in the Burning Expanse save for a small oasis that is surrounded by high, impassable cliffs in the southeastern corner of the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bête Noire</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/b%C3%AAte_noire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/b%C3%AAte_noire/</guid>
      <description>title: Bête Noire desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Bête_Noire percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Bête Noire Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The city of Bête Noire is located on the dark side of Kalijor, in the shadow of a mostly inactive volcano that bears the same name.
Bête Noire is a city rivaling Rathalon in size and population, partially because it is one of the only major cities in the world that allows sentients to get away with some of the darker things in life, namely thievery, scamming, prostitution, and the occasional &amp;lsquo;accidental&amp;rsquo; death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cohai Observatory</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/cohai_observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/cohai_observatory/</guid>
      <description>title: Cohai Observatory desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Cohai_Observatory percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Cohai Observatory Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Cohai Observatory is a keep that sits at the top of a spire of rock that thrusts up some three or four thousand feet from the western face of the Uraval Mountains . The only land based approach to Cohai is from a narrow pass in the Forest of Brume that leads to an ancient rope bridge spanning the two-hundred foot gap from the mountains to the spire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Sea</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/dead_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/dead_sea/</guid>
      <description>title: Dead Sea desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Dead_Sea percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Dead Sea Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Dead Sea is a large, rancid body of sickly, thick, green water that rests in the southern end of the Plain of Sorrow. This sea was once a life spring before it was corrupted by some unknown force that destroyed it and the ancient forest surrounding it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forest Of Brume</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/forest_of_brume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/forest_of_brume/</guid>
      <description>title: Forest Of Brume desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Forest_Of_Brume percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Forest of Brume Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Forest of Brume is an ancient forest that dominates more than a third of the light side of Kalijor. It rests between the Northern and Southern Planes of Serenity, runs up to the Uraval Mountains on the east side and the Great Sea to the west.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gelid Mountains</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/gelid_mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/gelid_mountains/</guid>
      <description>title: Gelid Mountains desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Gelid_Mountains percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Gelid Mountains Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Gelid Mountains are a range of low mountains that sit between the Southern Wastes and the Northern Wastes. The largest peak in the range is Mount Tellamon, the home of the city of Talanor. The mountains, although low in elevation are frigid cold year round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Inland Sea</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/great_inland_sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/great_inland_sea/</guid>
      <description>title: Great Inland Sea desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Great_Inland_Sea percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Great Inland Sea Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Great Inland Sea is the largest, land-locked body of water in Kalijor. It is surrounded by the Forest of Brume and on the southern and western shores lay the oldest parts of the forest. This huge body of water is dark and calm, relatively warm and, if you stay close to shore, safe for swimming in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isle Of Magic</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/isle_of_magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/isle_of_magic/</guid>
      <description>title: Isle Of Magic desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Isle_Of_Magic percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Isle of Magic Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Isle of magic is located two or three days sail from the Western shores of the Kalijor mainland. This island is where most of the world’s Fay folk have taken up residence in an attempt to remove themselves from the prying eyes of the overly inquisitive races of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loch Moore</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/loch_moore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/loch_moore/</guid>
      <description>title: Loch Moore desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Loch_Moore percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Loch Moore Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description Loch Moore is a small frontier town on the edge of the Burning Expanse. Its people are mostly simple farmers and live stock handlers, with a few artisans having taken up residence as the town becomes more and more popular among wayward adventurers on their way into the Burning Expanse in search of fortune and glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Academy</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/magic_academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/magic_academy/</guid>
      <description>title: Magic Academy desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Magic_Academy percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Magic Academy Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Magic Academy is the paragon of higher learning for mages in Kalijor. The structure itself is something of a curiosity. A two-hundred foot high monolith of solid stone set in a small clearing in the western Forest of Brume, it has one door at it&amp;rsquo;s base and can be walked around in less than a minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Wastes</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/northern_wastes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/northern_wastes/</guid>
      <description>title: Northern Wastes desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Northern_Wastes percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Northern Wastes Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Northern wastes is a region of snowy land nestled in a hollow depression on the west side of Mount Telemon. The hollow is surrounded on all sides by impassible mountains, making the only easy access to the Northern Wastes through the city of Talanor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onoba</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/onoba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/onoba/</guid>
      <description>title: Onoba desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Onoba percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Onoba Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description Onoba is the name given to the home of the Obscuri. While the Obscuri themselves are beyond such things as names, no attempt has been made to discourage the use of this name and so it has become the common name of their place of residence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandoria</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/pandoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/pandoria/</guid>
      <description>title: Pandoria desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Pandoria percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Pandoria Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description Pandoria is a city that was created in a pocket dimension. The only way to get to Pandoria is by one of the two portals that connect it to Kalijor. One is in the great portal chamber in Rathalon and the other is a larger portal that is deep within the forest of Brume .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Of Serenity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_serenity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_serenity/</guid>
      <description>title: Plain Of Serenity desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Plain_Of_Serenity percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Plain of Serenity Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Plane of Serenity is a huge expanse of grasslands that lay to the west of Rathalon and north of the Forest of Brume. These grasslands play host to most of the agriculture that feeds the many citizens of Rathalon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plain Of Sorrow</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_sorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/plain_of_sorrow/</guid>
      <description>title: Plain Of Sorrow desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Plain_Of_Sorrow percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Plain of Sorrow Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Plane of Sorrow is the name given to the area east of the Uraval Mountains. The entire area is collectively known as the dark side of Kalijor but the Plane of Sorrow is its actual name. This region is enormous, and featureless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rathalon</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/rathalon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/rathalon/</guid>
      <description>title: Rathalon desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Rathalon percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Rathalon Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The unofficial capital city of Kalijor , Rathalon is by far the largest city in the world. It was carved by the best dwarven craftsmen in the world along with assistance from some of the cleverest mages since the great wars. Not a single piece of stone was added to the city during its construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southern Plain Of Serenity</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_plain_of_serenity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_plain_of_serenity/</guid>
      <description>title: Southern Plain Of Serenity desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Southern_Plain_Of_Serenity percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Southern Plain of Serenity Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Southern Plane of Serenity rests between the southern edge of the Forest of Brume and the Northern edge of the Burning Expanse. On its western edge is the great sea and to the East is the Uraval Mountain&amp;rsquo;s southern tip and the great stone tree that is home to the city of Avian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southern Wastes</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_wastes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/southern_wastes/</guid>
      <description>title: Southern Wastes desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Southern_Wastes percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Southern Wastes Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The southern Wastes is a cold, snowy expanse that rests between the Northern gate of Rathalon and the southern entrance to Talanor. The area is almost always covered in snow, although it does clear up a bit in the summer months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talanor</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/talanor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/talanor/</guid>
      <description>title: Talanor desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Talanor percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Talanor Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description Talanor is the home of Kalijor&amp;rsquo;s Dwarves and Gnomes. It is a city that is carved out of the belly of Mount Telemon to the north of Rathalon, between the snowy Northern and Southern Wastes. The city maintains a constant level of lighting and temperature day and night, year round which makes it uncomfortable for most surface-dwelling people to handle on a continuous basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uraval Mountains</title>
      <link>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/uraval_mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kalijor.garibaldi0.com/encyclopedia/places-kalijor/uraval_mountains/</guid>
      <description>title: Uraval Mountains desc:
date: 2019/01/25 version: 1.0.0 template:
nav: Uraval_Mountains percent: 100 authors:
Vital Statistics Name: Uraval Mountains Other Names: Location: Permanent Population: Transient Population: Imports: Exports:
Description The Uraval Mountains are a range of extremely high, sheer-walled peaks that runs from the City of Rathalon (which is carved from the head of the mountain range), southward to Avian, dividing Kalijor cleanly in half and separating the light side and the dark side with an impassable wall of solid stone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>